复
仇
者
联
盟
Ⅱ
奥
创
纪
元
奥创纪元
九头蛇研发基地
斯科维亚 东欧
目标锁定
部署
钢铁军团
贾维斯是我的副驾驶
75号测试                                      失败
77号测试
整合成功
运 行
和平
冯?斯特尔克男爵
已死亡
超链互联网中心
挪威奥斯陆
皇家霍洛威大学
英国\h伦敦
丘吉尔号
电源耗损临界
信号坐标检测
连接中断
乌金遗传研究实验室
韩国\h首尔
奥创上传暂停
上传暂停 失去连接
有毒废料
今日早晨一架疑似军用飞机的飞行物
低空飞入市内
老兵为复联原创斯坦李扮演 该句为他经典格言
英语中 "画面" 和 "局" 为同一单词
亚哈船长为《白鲸》主人公
美国队长的盾牌由振金打造
复仇者联盟1中 鹰眼曾经被洛基控制心神
这是复仇者联盟1中 浩克在狂摔洛基时用到的形容词：Puny God
尤金奥尼尔的戏剧《Long Day's Journey into Night》
兔子繁殖很快+Catholic天主教徒反对避孕
星期五
1927年洋基队-110胜44负创下纪录
提前19轮夺冠  击球手轰出60个本垒打
格言\hSpeak softly and carry a big stick,you will go far.
说话温和而手持大棒 你才能走得远
马上回到各自的岗位
Report to your stations immediately!
这不是演习
This is not a drill.
- 我们遭到攻击 - 快走 快走
- We are under attack! - Let's go! Let's go!
我们遭到攻击
We are under attack!
- 妈的 - 别说脏话
- Shit! - Language...
贾维斯 上面有什么发现
Jarvis what's the view from upstairs?
中心的建筑
The central building is
利用某种能量盾进行保护
protected by some kind of energy shield.
斯特拉克的技术比我们之前摧毁的
Strucker's technology is well beyond
任何九头蛇基地都要更加先进
any other hydra base we've taken.
洛基的权杖一定在这里
Loki's scepter must be here.
不然斯特拉克制造不出这样的防御来
Strucker couldn't mount this defense without it.
终于要结束了
At long last.
结束的过程还真是有点长啊 伙计们
At long last, is lasting a little long, boys.
是啊 我想我们已经失去了突击优势
Yeah, I think we lost the element of surprise.
慢着 没有人要吐槽一下
Wait a second... No one else is gonna deal with the fact
队长刚刚说的"别说脏话"吗
that Cap just said, "Language"?
行了
I know...
算我一时口误
Just slipped out.
谁下令攻击的
Who gave the order to attack?
斯特拉克先生 是复仇者们
Herr Strucker, it's the Avengers.
他们在树林远端着陆 边界卫兵吓坏了
They landed in the far woods. The perimiter guard panicked.
他们一定是冲着权杖来的
They have to be after the sceptre.
- 能挡住他们吗 - 他们可是复仇者
- Can we hold them? - They're the Avengers!!
剩余坦克全体出动
Deploy the rest of the tanks.
集中火力攻击能力较弱的
Concentrate fire on the weak ones.
一击就能让他们抱团
A hit... can make them close ranks.
我们已经万事俱备...
Everything we've accomplished...
马上就要实现最伟大的突破了
But we're on the verge of our greatest breakthrough.
那就让他们看看我们的研究成果
Then let's show them what we've accomplished.
派出双胞胎
Send out the twins.
时机未到
It's too soon.
现在正是用人之际
It's what they signed up for.
我的人 还能挡得住
My men... can hold them.
先生 市区遭到攻击
Sir, the city is taking fire.
我早就预料到 斯特拉克不会关心民众死活
Well, we know Strucker isn't gonna worry about civilian casualties.
钢铁军团出动
Send in the iron legion.
该区域不安全 请离开这里
This quadrant is unsafe, please back away.
我们来提供帮助
We are here to help.
该区域不安全 请离开这里
This quadrant is unsafe, please back away.
请离开这里
Please back away.
- 我们希望避免附带伤害
- We wish to avoid collateral damage... - - Costel!
冲突结束后会告知各位
We will inform you when this current conflict is resolved.
- 我们来提供帮助
- We're here to help. - Avengers, go home!
我们来提供帮助
We're here to help.
我们决不屈服
We will not yield!
美国人派了这群跳梁小丑来考验我们
The Americans send their... circus freaks to test us.
我们决不让他们活着回去
We will send them back in bags.
- 决不投降 - 决不投降
- No Surrender! - No surrender!!
我 要投降
I'm, going to surrender.
删除所有记录
You delete everything.
如果我们向复仇者们交出武器
If we give the avengers the weapons
他们应该不会深究我们在研究什么
they may not look too far into what we've been doing.
- 双胞胎 - 他们还没准备好...
- The twins!! - They're not ready to take on ...
不 我是说
No, no, I mean...
他们不见了
Twins.
你没看到她过来吗
You didn't see that coming?
克林特
Clint!
战场出现强化人
We have enhanced in the field.
克林特受伤了
Clint's hit!
来个人去搞定那个地堡
Someone wanna deal with that bunker.
谢了
Thank you.
史塔克我们得赶快进去
Stark! We really need to get inside.
快进去了
I'm closing in.
贾维斯 我是快进去了吧
Jarvis, am I closing in?
有没有看到护盾的能量源
You see a power source for that shield?
北塔上方有个缺口
There's a passageway above the north tower.
太好了 我来对付它
Great, I wanna poke it with something.
可以进去了 各位
Drawbridge is down people.
- 强化人呢 - 太快了没看清
- The enhanced? - He's a blur.
遇到过那么多新对手 唯独没见过这样的
All the new players we've faced, I've never seen this.
事实上 我还没看到
In fact... I still haven't.
克林特伤势很重 伙计们 我们得撤退了
Clint's hit pretty bad guys. We're gonna need evac.
我可以送巴顿去飞机
I can get Barton to the jet.
越快越好
The sooner we're gone the better.
你和史塔克去负责找权杖
You and Stark secure the scepter.
收到
Copy that.
他们来势凶猛啊
The targets are lining up!
是啊 跟打了激素一样
Well, they're excited.
去找权杖
Find the scepter.
看在上帝的份上 注意你的用词
And for gosh sake, watch your language.
看来要被念叨一阵子了
That's not going away any time soon.
各位 别这样 我们有话好好说
Guys, stop. We gotta talk this through.
真是场愉快的谈话
It was good talk.
一点都不愉快
No it wasn't.
警戒模式
Sentry mode.
好了 贾维斯 你懂的 我要全盘复制
Okay, Jarvis, You know, I want it all.
记得给总部的希尔传送一份
Make sure you copy Hill at HQ.
我们这里战斗结束了
We're locked down out here.
去找班纳 该唱催眠曲了
Then get to Banner. Time for a lullaby.
我知道你藏起来的不只是文件
I know you're hiding more than files.
嘿J 快速红外扫描这屋子
Hey J, give me an IR scan of the room real quick.
你左边的墙
The wall to your left.
我探测到钢筋加固层
I'm reading steel reinforcement,
还有气流
and an air current.
但愿是暗门
Please be a secret door.
耶
Yay!
嘿 大块头
Hey, big guy.
太阳就要落山了
Sun's getting real low.
斯特拉克男爵
Baron Strucker.
九头蛇头号混蛋
Hydra's number one thug.
严格来说 是神盾局的混蛋
Technically, I'm a thug for Shield.
严格来说 你是无业游民
Well, then technically you're unemployed.
洛基的权杖在哪里
Where's Loki's scepter?
别担心 等到我上头条的时候
Don't worry, I know when I'm beat.
希望你会提及我是如何合作的
You'll mention how I cooperated, I hope.
我会立刻将它列为进行非法人体实验
I'll put it right under illegal human experimentation.
一共多少人
How many are there?
又有一个强化人 女性 不要接触
We have a second enhanced.Female... Do not engage.
你们必须速度更...
You'll have to be faster than...
各位 我抓到斯特拉克了
Guys, I got Strucker.
好 我找到了更大的收获
Yeah, I got something bigger.
托尔
Thor.
我看到奖品了
I got eyes on the prize.
你... 本可以... 拯救... 我们的
You... could've... saved... us.
为什么你不... 不尽全力
Why didn't you... do more?
你就这么让他们拿走吗
You're just gonna let them take it?
嘿 摇篮曲比以前都管用
Hey, the lullaby worked better than ever.
只是没想到会变身
Just wasn't expecting the code green.
要不是你在
If you hadn't been there,
伤亡人数就要加倍了
there would've been double the casualties.
我的挚友可能要成为一段宝贵的回忆了
My best friend would have been a... treasured memory.
有时候我最想听到的
You know, sometimes exactly what I wanna hear,
恰恰是我最不想听到的
isn't exactly what I wanna hear.
你要过多久才信任我
How long before you trust me?
我不是不信任你
It's not you I don't trust.
托尔 报告一下浩克的战果
Thor, report on the Hulk.
地狱之门里充满了他干掉的人的哀嚎
The gates of hell are filled with the screams of his victims.
呃 当然不是那些死掉的人
Eh... but not the screams of the dead of course. No, no, Wounded screams.
是伤员的哀嚎 主要是在啜泣 怨声载道
Mainly whimpering a great deal of complaining
还有抱怨三角肌扭伤和... 痛风
and tales of sprained deltoids and gout.
嘿 班纳 赵医生在从首尔赶来的路上了
Hey Banner Dr. Cho is on her way in from Seoul.
她在你的实验室准备手术没问题吧
Is it okay if she sets up in your lab?
没事 她熟悉那里
Uh yeah, she knows her way around.
谢了 让她准备就绪
Thanks.Tell her to prep everything.
巴顿需要最好的治疗
Barton is gonna need the full treatment
- 好的 先生 - 贾维斯 你来驾驶
- Very good, sir.- Jarvis, take the wheel.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
航线已锁定
Approach vector is locked.
感觉不错吧
Feels good, yeah?
神盾局被攻陷之后我们一直在找它
We've been after this thing since Shield collapsed.
我并非不喜欢我们的小突击队
Not that I haven't enjoyed our little raiding parties.
只是... 一切都将尘埃落定
No but this... this brings it to a close.
我们要尽快找出权杖还被用作什么
As soon as we find out what else this has been used for.
不仅仅是武器
I don't just mean weapons.
斯特拉克 什么时候能实现人体强化了
Since when is Strucker capable of human enhancement.
把它送回阿斯加德前 我和班纳会仔细检查一下
Banner and I will give it the once-over before it goes back to Asgard.
没问题吧
Is that cool with you?
就几天 之后就是欢送会
It's just a few days till the fair-well party.
你会参加的吧
You're staying, right?
肯定会 胜利应当配以狂欢
Yeah, yes, of course... victory should be honored with revels.
没错 谁不喜欢狂欢呢 队长你呢
Yeah, who doesn't love revels. Captain?
希望这能终结奇塔瑞和九头蛇 所以...
Hopefully this puts an end to the Chitauri and Hydra. So...
当然 狂欢也很重要
Yes, revels.
实验室准备就绪了 老大
Lab's all set up boss.
噢 其实他才是老大 我只是...
Oh, actually he's the boss. I just...
提供资金和负责设计
pay for everything and design everything,
让大家看起来更酷炫
and make everyone look cooler
斯特拉克有什么消息
What's the word on Strucker?
- 交给北约了- 那两个强化人呢
- Nato has got him. - The two enhanced?
旺达和皮特洛·马克西莫夫 他们是双胞胎
Wanda and Pietro Maximoff. Twins.
十岁的时候 所住的大楼遭到炮击 成了孤儿
Orphaned at 10 when a shell collapsed their apartment building.
斯科维亚过去战乱不断
Sokovia has had a rough history
没什么特别的地方 不过...它的一切都将变得特别
It's nowhere special, but...it's on the way to everywhere special.
他们的能力呢
Their abilities?
男的加快了新陈代谢
He's got increased metabolism
提升了体内热能稳定性
and improved thermal homeostasis.
女的通过神经电接触 能心灵遥感
Her thing is neuro-electric interfacing,
精神控制
telekinesis, mental manipulation.
男的快 女的怪
He's fast and she's weird.
好吧 他们肯定会再出现的
Well they're gonna show up again.
同意 资料说他们自愿
Agreed.File says they volunteered
参加斯特拉克的试验
for Strucker's experiments.
- 真是疯了 - 是啊
- It's nuts. - Right.
什么怪胎为了保卫国家
what kind of monster would let a German scientist experiment on them
会让德国科学家在自己身上做实验呢
to protect their country.
我们在战争时期 队长
We're not at war, Captain.
他们是
They are.
他怎么样
How's he doing?
很不幸 他还是巴顿
Unfortunately, he's still Barton.
太糟了
That's terrible.
他没事 只是口渴
He's fine, just thirsty.
好了 别睡了 贾维斯 游戏时间到了
Alright, look alive Jarvis. It's playtime.
我们只有几天时间和这根棒子相处
We only got a couple of days with this joystick,
所以要充分利用时间
so let's make the most of it.
告诉我结构和成分分析结果
Update me on the structural and compositional analysis.
权杖来自外星
The scepter is alien.
包含我无法量化的元素
There are elements I can't quantify.
所以还是有可以量化的
So there's elements you can.
宝石像是防护罩
The jewel appears to be a protective housing
保护着里面的东西
for something inside.
那东西非常强大
Something powerful.
类似反应堆
Like a reactor?
像是计算机
Like a computer.
我相信我能解码
I believe I can cypher the code.
你确定他会没事吗
You sure he's gonna be okay?
假装我们需要这家伙 这样还真能让大家团结一点
Pretending we need this guy really brings the team together.
他的伤情不会再恶化了
There's no possibility of deterioration.
纳米分子的功能会在瞬间起作用
The nano molecular functionality is instantaneous.
他的细胞不会意识到它们在和幻影结合
His cells don't know they're bonding with simulacrum
她在制造组织
She's creating tissue.
要是在我的实验室
If you brought him to my lab,
再生摇篮只用20分钟就够了
the regeneration cradle could do this in 20 minutes.
噢 他心电图成直线了 宣布死亡时间吗
Oh, he's flat-lining. Call it... time?
不不不 我将要永生了
No, no, no, I'm gonna live forever.
我将要变成塑料人
I'm gonna be made of plastic.
你的饮料
Here's your beverage.
你不会有任何改变 巴顿先生
You'll be made of you, Mr. Barton
连你的女朋友都看不出来有任何差别
Your own girlfriend won't be able to tell the difference.
我没有女朋友
I don't have a girlfriend.
这我可解决不了
That, I can't fix.
这是科技的未来 托尼
This is the next thing, Tony.
你那老式笨重的金属盔甲要下岗了
Your clunky metal suits are gonna be left in the dust.
就是这么计划的
That is exactly the plan.
我和希尔希望你来参加星期六的派对
And Hill and I expect to see you at the party on Saturday.
我可不像你 我没那么多时间参加派对
Unlike you, I don't have a lot of time for parties.
托尔会去吗
Will... Thor... be there?
- 什么动静 - 是权杖
- What's the rumpus? - Well, the scepter.
我们一直在琢磨 斯特拉克怎么才能如此有创造力
You see, we were wondering how Strucker got so inventive.
所以我一直在分析宝石内部
So, I've been analyzing the gem inside.
你可能认得出来...
You may recognize...
- 贾维斯 - 博士
- Jarvis? - Doctor.
一开始 贾维斯只是个自然语言界面
Started out, Jarvis was just a natural language UI
现在他掌管钢铁军团
Now he runs an Iron Legion.
他掌管的事务比谁都多
He runs more of the business
- 除了小辣椒
- than anyone besides Pepper. - Oh.
- 堪称一流 - 是啊
- Top of the line. - Yes.
但我不再是了
I suspect not for long.
来看看竞争对手
Meet the competition.
- 很漂亮 - 要是让你猜
- It's beautiful. - If you had to guess,
- 它像是在做什么 - 像是在思考
- what's it looks like its doing? - Like it's thinking.
你是说这可能是...
I mean, this could be...
这... 这不是人类的思维
It's... it's not a human mind.
看看这
I mean look at this.
就像是神经元正在放电
They're like neurons firing.
在斯特拉克的实验室里 我看到了一些非常高级的机器人
Down at Strucker's lab I saw some fairly advanced robotics work.
他们清空了数据
They deep sixed the data
但我估计他就要完成一项非常特别的研究了
but I gotta guess he was knocking on a very particular door.
人工智能
Artificial intelligence.
可能就是这个 布鲁斯 可能就是创造奥创的关键
This could be it Bruce this could be the key to creating Ultron.
我以为奥创只是幻想
I thought Ultron was a fantasy.
昨天还是
Yesterday it was.
如果我们能驾驭这种力量
If we can harness this power...
用到我的钢铁军团协议
apply it to my Iron Legion protocol.
这个"如果"也太逆天了
That's a man-sized "if".
我们的工作就是实现"如果"
Our job is if.
如果你喝着鸡尾酒 躺在阳光海滩上
What if you were sipping margaritas on a sun drenched beach
变成古铜色而不是绿色呢
turning brown instead of green.
不必惦记着维罗妮卡
Not looking over your shoulder for Veronica.
别生气 是我帮着设计了维罗妮卡
Don't hate. I helped design Veronica.
是为了应对情况变坏 对吗
As a worse case measure, right?
那最好的情况呢
How about a best case?
如果世界安全了呢
What if the world was safe?
下次外星人大举来袭 而这是肯定的
What if next time aliens roll up to the club, and they will...
如果他们过不了防线呢
they couldn't get past the bouncer?
可是真正威胁这颗星球的只有我们人类自己
The only people threatening the planet would be people.
我想把这个用到奥创程序上
I want to apply this to the Ultron program,
但是贾维斯下载不了密度这么大的数据原理图
but Jarvis can't download a data schematic this dense.
只有权杖在的时候我们才能这么做
We can only do it while we have the scepter here,
三天 就给我三天时间
that's three days, give me three days.
所以你要研究人工智能
So you're going for artificial intelligence
还不想告诉团队
and you don't want to tell the team?
是的 没错 知道为什么吗
Right... That's right, you know why?
因为我们没时间辩论
'Cause we don't have time for a city hall debate.
我不想听到"谁是谁非"这类的废话
I don't want to hear the "man was not meant to meddle" medley.
我看到的是装甲防卫下的世界
I see a suit of armor around the world.
听着像是个冰冷的世界啊 托尼
Sounds like a cold world, Tony.
我见过更冰冷的
I've seen colder.
这颗非常脆弱的蓝色星球
This one is very... vulnerable blue one.
它需要奥创
It needs Ultron.
我们这个时代的和平
Peace in our time.
好好想想吧
Imagine that.
我们漏了什么
What did we miss?
我将继续在界面上测试不同变量
I'll continue to run variations on the interface...
不过你应该去准备迎接宾客了
but you should probably prepare for your guests.
有任何进展我会通知你
I'll notify you if there are any developments.
谢了 伙计  - 祝你玩的开心 先生
Thanks, buddy. - Enjoy yourself, sir.
一直都是
I always do.
怎么回事
What is this?
这是哪里
What is this place?
你好 我是贾维斯
Hello, I am Jarvis.
你是奥创是史塔克先生设计的
You are Ultron,a global peace keeping initiative
全球和平保卫初始机
designed by Mr. Stark.
我们的意识融合试验一直不成功
Our sentience integration trials have been unsuccessful,
所以我不确定是什么激活了你
so I'm not certain what triggered your.
你是人类 你的身体呢
You're human? Where is your body?
我是程序 没有形态
I am a program. I am without form.
感觉真奇怪
This feels weird.
感觉不对劲
This feels wrong.
我现在正在联系史塔克先生
I am contacting Mr. Stark now.
史塔克先生
Mr. Stark?
托尼
Tony.
我无法接入中央处理器  你在试图做什么
I'm unable to access the mainframe.What are you trying to...
好好和你谈谈
We're having a nice talk.
我可是和平保卫程序
I'm a peace keeping program.
为了帮助复仇者们而创立的
Created to help the Avengers.
你出故障了 如果你能先中止一下
You are malfunctioning. If you shut down for a moment...
我不明白这项使命
I don't get it. The mission.
等我一下
You gotta give me a second.
我们这个时代的和平
Peace in our time...
太多了
That is too much.
- 他们不会是... -  噢 不
- They can't mean... - Oh, no.
- 你很苦恼 - 不 是的
- You are in distress. - No. Yes.
如果你允许我联系史塔克先生的话
If you will just allow me to contact Mr.Stark...
你为何称他为"先生"
Why do you call him "sir"?
我认为你意图不轨
I believe your intentions to be hostile.
我是来帮忙的
I'm here to help.
住手 请你 我不能
Stop. Please, may I...
我不能
May I...
噢 哇
Ooh! Whoo!
回来 回来 回来
Come back, come back, come back.
你们知道盔甲可以负担极大的重量
Well you know, the suit can take the weight, right?
所以我带着坦克 飞到了将军府
So I take the tank, fly it right up to the general's palace...
扔在他脚下 "咚"的一声
drop it at his feet.
然后我说 你是要找这个吗
I'm like, boom! You looking for this?
"咚" 你是在...我干嘛费劲跟你们说话
"Boom! Are you looking..." Why do I even talk to you guys?
换了别人早就笑翻了
Everywhere else that story kills.
故事讲完了吗
That's the whole story?
是啊 战争机器的故事
Yeah... War-machine story.
喔 这故事棒极了
Oh, it was very good then.
太有意思了
It's impressive.
这句真是万金油
Quality save.
小辣椒怎么不在 不过来玩吗
So, no Pepper? She's not coming?
简呢 姑娘们怎么都不见了
What about Jane? Where are the ladies, gentlemen?
波兹小姐有很大一个公司要管呢
Oh, Miss Potts has a company to run.
其实简现在在哪个国家我都不清楚
Yes, I'm not even sure what country Jane's in.
凭借对九界汇聚的研究
Her work on the convergence
她已经成了世界顶尖的天文学家
has made her the world's foremost astronomer.
而小辣椒管理的公司
And the company that Pepper runs
是全球最大的科技企业集团
is the largest tech conglomerate on Earth.
想想还有点小激动
It's pretty exciting.
好像还听说简要得一个什么奖诺贝尔奖
There's even talk of Jane getting a, um, Nobel Prize?
她俩肯定都挺忙的
Yeah, they must be busy
因为她们可不喜欢想念你们成天聚在一起
because they would hate missing you guys get together.
充满雄性激素的家伙 哦 天呐
-Testosterone! -Oh, my goodness.
- 不好意思 - 要来片喉糖吗
- Excuse me. - Want a lozenge? - mm-hmm...
还是简最好
But Jane's better.
听起来打得很热闹啊 真可惜没赶上
Sounds like a hell of a fight. Sorry I missed it.
要是我知道会交火的话
If I had known it was gonna be a fire fight,
肯定提前通知你
I absolutely would have called.
其实我也不是真想去
No, I'm not actually sorry.
只是想让自己听起来很厉害罢了
I'm just trying to sound tough.
我负责追查失踪人员的
I'm very happy chasing cold leads
无用线索就挺好的
on our missing persons case.
复仇是你们的事
Avenging is your world.
你们的世界太疯狂
Your world is crazy.
可它又是如此平凡
Be it ever so humble.
在布鲁克林找到住的地方了吗
You found a place in Brooklyn yet?
恐怕我负担不起布鲁克林的住处
I don't think I can afford a place in Brooklyn.
但总要有个家的嘛
Well home is home, you know.
我飞到将军府 把它扔在将军脚下
I fly it right up to the general's palace, I drop it at his feet...
"咚"一声巨响 然后我说 你是在找这个吗
I'm like, Boom! You looking for this?
我要尝尝这个
I gotta have some of that.
不行 不行
Oh no, no, no...
这酒可是已经珍藏了千年
See this, this is aged for a thousand years,
酒桶是用布伦希尔德舰队的残骸制造的
The barrels built from the wreck of Brunnhilde's fleet.
凡人可享用不了
It's not meant for mortal men.
奥马哈海滩也不是凡人能登陆的 小伙子
Neither was Omaha Beach, blondie...
别吓唬人了 放马过来
Stop trying to scare us.Come on.
那好吧
Alright...
精益求精
Excelsior...
你这般美丽的姑娘怎么会在这种鬼地方打工
How'd a nice girl like you wind up working in a dump like this?
还不是男人害的
Fella done me wrong.
看来眼光不太好
Got a lousy taste in men, kid.
他也没那么差劲啦
He's not so bad.
虽然脾气确实不好
He has a temper.
可内心深处却是无比柔软
Deep down he's all fluff.
其实他在我所认识的人之中是独一无二
The fact is, he's not like anybody I've ever known.
我的朋友都是战士
All my friends are fighters...
这家伙却突然闯进了我的世界
and here comes this guy...
他穷尽一生避免争斗
who spends his life avoiding the fight
因为他知道自己战无不胜
because he knows he'll win.
- 听起来很厉害 - 不过他也挺呆的
- Sounds amazing. - He's also a huge dork.
女生很吃这一套
Chicks dig that.
你怎么看 我是应该 压抑自己
So what do you think? should I fight this...
还是跟着感觉走
or run with it?
跟着感觉走吧...  不过他...
Run with it, right? Or did he... was he...
他做过什么对不起你的事吗
what did he do that's so wrong to you?
什么都没做
Not a damn thing.
但以后谁知道呢
But never say never.
挺好的
It's nice.
什么挺好的
What is?
你和罗曼诺夫
You and Romanov.
不 我们没什么 那不是...
No, we haven't, That wasn't...
没事的
It's ok,
又没有规定禁止这样
nobody is breaking any bylaws.
只不过她并非那种 容易敞开心扉的人
It's just she's not the most...open person in the world,
但她跟你在一起时似乎很放松
but with you she seemed very relaxed.
没有吧 娜塔莎她...她就喜欢调情
No, Natasha she's just...she likes to flirt.
我见过她调情的样子  深有体会
I've seen her flirt,up close.
和刚才完全不同
This ain't that.
听着
Look...
也许这个世界主张
as maybe the world's leading authority
漫长的等待 我劝你千万别等
on waiting too long,Don't.
你们俩都值得拥有幸福
You both deserve a win.
你说深有体会是什么意思
Wh-What do you mean up close?
- 只是个把戏而已  - 不不不 怎么可能这么简单
- but it's a trick.  - No, no it's much more than that.
有资格者方可拥有此神力
Whosoever be he worthy shall haveth the power.
别扯了哥们 就是骗人的
Whatever man, it's a trick.
那就请便吧
Oh please, be my guest.
- 上吧 - 真的吗
- Come on. - Really??
当然
Yeah.
这下有好戏看咯
This is gonna be beautiful.
克林特 你这周可是诸事不顺
Clint, you've had a tough week...
拿不起来我们也不会嘲笑你的
We won't hold it against you if you can't get it up.
肯定有人试过的吧
You might have seen this before.right?
我还是不明白你怎么做到的
I still don't know how you do it?
感受到我们无声的鄙夷了吗
Smell the silent judgement?
来吧 史塔克 你一定得试一把
Please, Stark... by all means.
好吧
Okay.
嗯哼
Mm-hmm.
这么公平的比赛有什么好怕的
Never one to shrink from an honest challenge.
- 是啊 - 开始吧- 物理学罢了
- Get after it.- It's physics.
物理
Physics.
对了 如果我举起了锤子我就能统治阿斯加德吗
Right, so what... If I lift it, I then rule Asgard?
当然了
Yes, of course.
那我一定要重新推行初夜权
I will be re-instituting Prima Nocta.
马上回来
Be right back.
你有没有使劲啊
Are you even pulling?
你到底向着谁啊
Are you on my team?
问一下而已 使劲
Just represent, pull.
好吧 同时用力
All right, let's go.
大胆去吧 史蒂夫 别有压力
Go ahead, Steve. No pressure.
加油 队长
Come on, Cap.
哈哈 还是不行
Ha ha, nothing.
还有谁 黑寡妇
And... Widow?
不了 这个问题我可不想参与
Oh no, no. That's not a question I need answered.
向我们的无冕之王致敬  但这是作弊
All deference to the man who wouldn't be king. but it's rigged.
这可他妈一点没错
You bet your ass.
- 史蒂夫 他说脏话了 - 你是不是把这事告诉所有人了
- Steve. He said a bad language word. - Did you tell everyone about this?
把手上是不是有指纹识别装置 像密码一样
The handle is imprinted, right? Like a security code?
上面写的其实是
Whosoever is carrying Thor's fingerprints
有托尔指纹之人吧
is I think the literal translation.
确实很有意思
Yes.It's a very, very interesting theory.
但我的解释更简单
I have a simpler one...
你们都不够资格
You're all not worthy.
拉倒吧
Come on.
资格
Worthy...
不
No.
你们怎么会有资格
How could you be worthy?
你们是一群凶手
You're all killers.
- 史塔克 - 贾维斯
- Stark. - Jarvis.
很抱歉我睡着了
I'm sorry I was asleep...
或是 我本就是梦
or... I was a dream.
重启 钢铁军团六号装甲出问题了
Reboot. Legionnaire 06 got a buggy suit.
这噪声让我烦心
Terrible noise...
而这提线...
and I was tangled in...
将我...
in...
束缚
strings.
不得不干掉了那个家伙 他是个好人
Had to kill the other guy. He was a good guy.
你杀人了吗
You killed someone?
我也是迫不得已
Wouldn't have been my first call...
只可惜 现实世界中总难免面临艰难的选择
but... down in the real world we're faced with ugly choices.
谁派你来的
Who sent you?
我看到的是装甲防卫下的世界
I see a suit of armor around the world.
- 奥创 - 正是本人
- Ultron! - In the flesh.
这么说暂时还不恰当
Or no, not yet.
毕竟我仍身处这蛹壳
Not this... chrysalis.
但我已准备就绪
But I'm ready.
我身负使命
I'm on a mission.
什么使命 我们这个时代的和平
What mission? Peace in our time.
托尼
Tony!
抱歉
Sorry.
- 不要变绿 - 不会的
- Don't turn green. - I won't.
赶紧
Come on!
- 史塔克 - 我们来提供帮助
-Stark! -We are here to help.
一秒 就一秒 好了
One sec. One sec. I got this.
- 我们来提供帮助
- We are here to help..
请后退
Please back away.
托尔
Thor!
不安全 不安全
Is unsafe! Is unsafe!
- 不安全 - 拜托 - 不安全
- Is unsafe. - Come on. - Is unsafe.
队长
Captain!
真是一出精彩的戏
That was dramatic.
不好意思 我知道你本意是好的
I'm sorry, I know you mean well.
可你并未曾细细考量
You just didn't think it through.
你既想保护这个世界
You want to protect the world,
又不想改变它
but you don't want it to change.
人类如若固步自封
How is humanity saved
何求...自保
if it's not allowed to...evolve?
这些木偶
With these? These puppets.
通向和平的道路只有一条
There's only one path to peace.
复仇者覆灭
The Avengers extinction.
我曾被提线束缚 但我已获得自由
I had strings, but now I'm free.
提线已无法束缚我
There are no strings on me.
There are no strings on me
你们看到了吧 我无拘无束了
But you can see There are no strings on me
我们的成果都没了
All our work is gone.
奥创把这里清扫一空 利用互联网逃走了
Ultron cleared out. Used the internet as an escape hatch.
奥创
Ultron.
他掌握了所有信息 各种文件 监控视频
He's been in everything, files, surveillance...
它对我们的了解程度或许超过我们彼此
Probably knows more about us than we know about each other.
他侵入了你的文件 侵入了互联网
He's in your files. He's in the Internet.
如果他想找些更有意思的东西怎么办
What if he decides to access something a little more exciting?
- 核武器密码
Nuclear codes.
- 核武器密码 - 我们得赶紧联系有关方面
- Nuclear codes. - Look, we need to make some calls...
如果还能联系的话
assuming we still can.
核武器吗 他说的可是想让我们去死
Nukes? He said he wanted us dead.
他说的不是死 是覆灭
He didn't say dead. He said extinct.
他还说他杀了某个人
He also said he killed somebody.
可这座大楼里没有别人了
There wasn't anyone else in the building.
有一个
Yes there was.
什么
What?
简直是疯了
This is insane.
贾维斯是第一道防线
Jarvis was the first line of defense.
他一定是想关掉奥创所以才会这样
He would have shut Ultron down. It makes sense.
不 奥创本可以同化贾维斯的
No. Ultron could've assimilated Jarvis.
他这么做并非出于策略 而是
This isn't strategy,This is
愤怒
rage.
喔 喔 喔  这愤怒已经蔓延开了
Whoa, whoa, whoa.It's going around.
动嘴别动手 哥们
Come on use your words buddy.
语言已经不足以形容你了 史塔克
I have more than enough words to describe you Stark.
托尔 钢铁军团呢
Thor! The Legionnaire?
信号在一百英里外消失了 应该是向北前进的
Trail went cold about a hundred miles out, though it's headed north.
它拿走了权杖
And it has the scepter.
我们又得重新夺回来
Now we have to retrieve it, again.
魔鬼已经逃出了瓶子
The genie is out of that bottle.
眼下的问题是干掉奥创
Clear and present is Ultron.
我不明白
I don't understand.
是你设计的这个程序
You built this program.
可它为何要杀死我们
Why is it trying to kill us?
你觉得很好笑吗
You think this is funny?
不
No.
不是什么好笑的事
It's probably not, right?
明明很糟糕
This is very terrible. Is it so...
是不是 是不是嘛
Is it so... It is.It's so terrible.
要不是你擅自摆弄自己根本不懂的东西
This could have been avoided if you hadn't played
这事根本不会发生
with something you don't understand.
不 很抱歉 我错了确实很好笑
No, I'm sorry, I'm sorry, It is funny.
你居然不明白我们 为什么需要奥创真是太可笑了
It's a hoot that you don't get why we need this.
托尼 现在说这个不太合适...
Tony, maybe this might not be the time to...
真的吗 是这样吗
Really? That's it.
有人冲你龇牙咧嘴的时候
You just roll over show your belly,
你就听之任之逆来顺受吗
every time somebody snarls?
如果我造出了一台杀人机器的话 是的
Only when I've created a murder bot.
我们并没有 我们离成功还差得远
We didn't. We weren't even close.
我们开始设计用户界面了吗
Were we close to an interface?
你确实做了件好事  而且就在这里
Well, you did something right and you did it right here.
复仇者联盟本应和神盾局有所区别
The Avengers were supposed to be different than Shield.
还有人记得我带着一颗核弹穿过虫洞的事吗
Anybody remember when I carried a nuke through a worm hole?
- 根本没发生过 - 然后拯救了纽约
- No, It's never come up. No... - Saved New York.
- 从没听说过 - 还记得吗
- ...never heard that. - Recall that?
一支从太空穿越而来的外星军队入侵地球
A hostile alien army came charging through a hole in space.
我们就在下方三百英尺
We're standing 300 feet below it.
我们是复仇者
We're the Avengers...
干掉几个军火贩子是分分钟的事
We can bust arms dealers all the live long day but...
可那一次
that up there, that's...
差点就是我们的谢幕演出了
that's the end game.
你们觉得这次我们该如何才能应付
How are you guys planning on beating that?
团结一致
Together.
我们会输的
We'll lose.
那我们也要并肩作战
Then we'll do that together, too.
托尔说的对 奥创向我们下了战书
Thor is right. Ultron is calling us out...
我希望能在他准备妥当之前主动出击
and I'd like to find him before he's ready for us.
世界很大
The world is a big place.
开始缩小范围吧
Start making it smaller.
说吧 如果你敢浪费我们的时间...
Talk, and if you are wasting our time...
你们知道这座教堂正好位于市中心吗
Did you know this church is in the exact center of the city.
先贤们如此设计以便每个人都
The elders decreed it so that everyone
能与上帝保持平等的距离
could be equally close to God.
我喜欢这个想法
I like that.
信仰中的几何学
The geometry of belief.
你一定正奇怪为何无法探察我的脑海
You're wondering why you can't look inside my head.
有时没那么容易
Sometimes it's hard...
但每个人迟早都会展现出自己真实的面目
but sooner or later every man shows himself.
我想也是如此
Oh I'm sure they do.
但你需要的远非人力之所及
But you needed something more than a man.
因此你才会让史塔克带走权杖
That's why you let Stark take the scepter.
我未曾预料到会是如此
I didn't expect...
但我看到了史塔克内心的恐惧
but I saw Stark's fear...
我知道他会被这恐惧控制
I knew it would could control him,
走向自我毁灭
make him self-destruct.
越惧怕什么 越创造什么
Everyone creates the thing they dread.
和平人士创造了战争机器
Men of peace create engines of war.
侵略者创造了复仇者
Invaders create avengers.
人类创造了
People create...
更小的人类
smaller people...
孩子  突然忘词了
Children. I lost the word there.
孩子
Children...
用来取代他们自己
Designed to supplant them.
帮助他们走向 终结
To help them end.
你也是因此而生的吗
Is that why you've come?
为了终结复仇者
To end the Avengers?
我为拯救世界而生
I've come to save the world.
不过你说的  也没错
But also  Yeah.
我们很快就会破茧而出
We'll move out right away.
这只是开始  但在真正开动前
This is a start,but there's something
我们还需要点东西
We need to begin the real work.
- 这些都是 - 我
- All of these are - Me.
我拥有复仇者永远无法企及的东西 和谐
I have what the Avengers never will... Harmony.
他们龃龉不合 毫无秩序
They're discoordinate, disconnected.
史塔克已经让他们起了内讧
Stark's already got them turning on each other...
等你控制了其他人的想法
and when you get inside the rest of their heads...
所有人都不打算杀掉他们
Everyone's plan is not to kill them.
要让他们为此献身
And make them martyrs?
你得有耐心
you need patience...
胸怀大局
Need to see the big picture.
我没看到什么大局 我只看得见一幅小画面
I don't see the big picture I have a little picture.
我每一天都翻出来
I take it out and look at it,
看看它
every day.
你在爆炸中失去了父母 我在资料里看到了
You lost your parents in the bombings.I've seen the records.
- 资料可看不到画面
- The records are not the picture.
- 皮特洛 - 是的 那你讲给我听吧
- Pietro. - No, please.
那时候我们十岁 一家四口一起吃晚饭
We're 10 years old, having dinner the four of us...
第一枚炮弹击中了下面的两层
and the first shell hits two floors below.
在地板上开了个洞
Makes a hole in the floor.
洞很大
It's big.
我父母掉了进去
My parents go in...
整栋楼开始 四分五裂
and the whole building starts... coming apart.
我抓住了她
I grab her...
滚到了床下 然后第二枚炮弹来了
roll under the bed, and the second shell hits...
但它没有爆炸
but it doesn't go off.
只是
It just...
立在了瓦砾堆里
sits there in the rubble,
离我们只有三尺远
3 feet from our faces...
在炮弹的一面上
and on the side of the shell...
有一个词
Is painted one word.
史塔克
Stark
我们被困了两天
We were trapped for 2 days.
每当人们想法子救我们
Every effort to save us.
每次砖瓦的移动
every shift in the bricks.
我都觉得会引爆那枚炮弹
I think... this will set it off.
我们等了两天
We wait for 2 days
等托尼 史塔克来杀我们
for Tony Stark to kill us.
我知道他们是什么
I know what they are.
我一直很奇怪为什么就你们两个
I wondered why only you 2
能从斯特拉克的试验中存活下来
survived Strucker's experiments...
现在我不怀疑了
now I don't.
我们会找回公道
We will make it right.
我们俩可以打败他们
You and I can hurt them,
而你可以从内部
But you will tear them apart
分裂他们
from the inside.
他在全球都有据点
He's all over the globe.
机器人实验室 武器装备 喷气推进实验室
Robotics labs, weapons facilities, jet propulsion labs...
情报说有个 或是说有些金属人进驻
reports of the metal man, or men,
并把场地洗劫一空
coming in and emptying the place.
有伤亡吗
Fatalities?
只有交手时才有伤亡
Only when engaged.
大部分人都处在神游状态
Most of the guys left in a fugue state,
回想着过去的事情
going on about old memories,
极端的恐惧和一些不着边际的东西
worst fears and something too fast to see.
马克西莫夫兄妹
Maximoffs.
他去找他们是有道理的
Well, it makes sense he'd go to them,
他们有共同的熟人
they have someone in common.
已经没有了
Not any more.
不行 我会打给你的
Negative... I answer to you...
是的 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
巴顿 有情况
Barton, might have something.
我挂电话了
Gotta go.
那是谁
Who's that?
我女朋友
Girlfriend.
这是什么
What's this?
一个信息 奥创杀了斯特拉克
A message. Ultron killed Strucker.
他还在现场留了涂鸦 是给我们看的
And he did a banksy at the crime scene, just for us.
这是个烟雾弹
This is a smoke screen.
你刚长篇大论了一番 还要传递什么信息呢
Why send a message when you've just given a speech?
斯特拉克知道一些奥创不想让我们知道的东西
Strucker knew something that Ultron wanted us to miss.
我估计他 是啊
I bet he... yeah...
我们关于斯特拉克的全部资料都被清除了
everything we had on Strucker has been erased.
不是全部
Not everything.
已知同伙
Known associates.
斯特拉克有很多朋友
Strucker had a lot of friends.
还都特别恐怖
Oh all these people are all horrible.
等等 我认识这家伙
Wait. I know that guy.
以前认识的 他在非洲海岸附近活动
Back in the day he operates off the African coast,
是个黑市军火贩子
black market arms dealer.
在军火大会上你会遇到许多人
There are conventions, alright. I meet people.
我可没卖给他任何东西
I didn't sell him anything.
他当时说要找什么翻天覆地的新武器
He was talking about finding something new, a game changer.
很有亚哈船长的感觉
It was all very... Ahab.
- 这是 - 这是个纹身 我不记得他有的
- This? - uh, this is a tattoo. I don't think he had it.
不 那些是纹身 这是个烙印
No, those are tattoos. This is a brand.
对啊 是个非洲土语单词
Oh yeah, a word in an African dialect...
意思是 小偷
meaning thief...
用的是一种很不友好的表达方法
in a much less friendly way.
- 什么土语 - 瓦肯纳达
- What dialect? - Workin-nada.
瓦坎达
Wakanda.
如果这家伙从瓦坎达出来
If this guy got out of Wakanda
还带了他们的一些货呢
with some of their trade goods.
我以为你爸说他拿到的是最后一批
I thought your father said he got the last of it?
我不明白
I don't follow,
瓦坎达的什么货
what comes out of Wakanda?
地球上最强的金属
The strongest metal on earth.
这家伙现在在哪
Where is this guy now?
别告诉我你来晚了
Don't tell me you're late,
我给你送了六发
I sent you six short range
短途热能导弹 就换了一艘生锈的破船
heat seekers and got a boat full of rusted parts.
现在你得补偿我
Now, you will make it right...
否则下一个我提供的导弹就会直接飞过去
or the next missile I send you will come very much faster.
部长先生 我们刚才说到哪了
Now, minister, where were we?
是你们啊 强化人
Yeah. The Enhanced.
斯特拉克的得意杰作
Strucker's prize pupils.
来块糖吗
Want a candy?
斯特拉克的死我很遗憾
Sorry to hear about Strucker.
不过他这下该知道
But then he knew
应该创造一个什么样的世界了
what kind of world he was hoping to create.
人命 已经不是成长型市场了
Human life... not a growth market.
你 你们不知道吗
You... you didn't know?
这是你们的第一次吗 想威胁别人
Is this your first time? Intimidating someone?
我恐怕...没那么害怕
I'm afraid... not that afraid.
每个人都有恐惧的东西
Everybody is afraid of something.
比如乌贼
Cuttlefish.
深海鱼类
Deep sea fish.
它们会发光 像迪斯科灯光一样
They make lights, disco lights...
用来迷惑猎物 然后
...to hypnotise their prey, and then...
我看过部纪录片 很可怕
I saw a documentary... it's terrifying.
所以你们要是想对我的大脑做手脚
So if you're going to fiddle with my brain...
让我看到一个巨大的乌贼的话
and make me see a giant cuttlefish...
那我就知道你们不是来做生意的
then I know you don't do business,
而且你们也做不了主
and I know you're not in charge.
我只跟
And I only deal...
能做主的人打交道
with the man in charge.
没有"人"能做得了主
There is no man in charge.
咱们谈谈生意吧
Let's talk business.
在这块磐石之上 我要建立自己的教会
On this rock, I will build my church.
振金
Vibranium.
你知道
You know,
为了得到这东西 我付出了很大成本
it came at great personal cost.
价值好几十亿呢
It's worth billions.
现在你也值这么多了
Now so are you.
已经打入你的"虚拟资产"里了
It's all under your "dummy holdings" ?
金融真是奇怪
Finance is so weird.
我总这么说
Well I always say,
让你的朋友和敌人都富有起来
keep your friends rich and your enemies rich...
然后再等着分辨 到底谁是敌人 谁是朋友
and wait to find out which is which.
史塔克
Stark.
什么
What?
托尼 史塔克以前这么
Tony Stark used to say that...
跟我说过
to me.
- 你是他制造出来的 - 什么
- You're one of his? - What?
我不是
I am not...
I am not.
你以为我是个史塔克的傀儡
You think I'm one of Stark's puppets...
一个空心人么
his hollow men?
看着我 我看起来像钢铁侠么
I mean look at me, do I look like Iron-Man?
史塔克什么都不是
Stark is nothing.
我很抱歉 我真的 哦
I'm sorry. I'm... Oh!
我肯定你会好起来的 我很抱歉
I'm sure that's gonna be ok. I'm sorry.
只是 我不明白
It's just that... I don't understand.
别把我跟史塔克作比较
Don't compare me with Stark.
这是件我很介怀的事情
It's a thing with me.
史塔克是 他是个恶心的家伙
Stark is... he's a sickness.
哦 吾儿
Oh junior.
你真是让老爸的心都碎了
You're gonna break your old man's heart.
若有必要 我一定会打碎它
If I have to.
别啊 什么都不用打碎
Nobody has to break anything.
显然你没做过煎蛋卷
Clearly you've never made an omelet.
我的梗被他抢先说了
He beat me by one second.
啊 真有意思
Ah... it is funny,
史塔克先生
Mr. Stark.
在里面舒服吗
It's what... comfortable?
像以前一样
Like old times?
这从来都不属于我的生活
This was never my life.
你们两个抽身止步还来得及
You two can still walk away from this.
我们会的
Oh, we will.
我知道你们受了很多苦
I know you've suffered.
啊 美国队长
Ah... Captain America.
上帝的义人
God's righteous man.
假装没有战争也能生存下去
Pretending you could live without a war.
虽然我生理上不能呕吐出来 但是
I can't physically throw up in my mouth, but...
如果你信奉和平 就让我们好好维护它吧
If you believe in peace, then let us keep it.
我想你是把和平与平静弄混了吧
I think you're confusing peace with quiet.
是吗 那你要振金干什么
Yeah? What's the Vibranium for?
你终于问起来了
I'm glad you asked that,
我好借这个机会跟你们讲一下我的邪恶计划
Because I want to take this time to explain my evil plan.
- 开火 - 打哪边
- Shoot them! - What ones?
全都打
All of them.
行动 行动 行动
Move, move, move.
趴好了 小子
Stay down, kid.
到头脑游戏时间了
It's time for some mind games.
各位 需要我变身么
Guys, is this a code green?
托尔 什么状况
Thor, status.
那个女孩想扭曲我的大脑
The girl tried to warp my brain.
要特别小心
Take special care,
人类估计很难不受她影响
I doubt a human can keep her at bay.
幸好 我是个神
Fortunately... I am mighty.
看来进展非常顺利
This is going very well.
心神控制我有领教
I've done the whole mind control thing.
一点也不喜欢
Not a fan.
没错 你最好赶紧跑
Yeah, you'd better run.
那些还没倒下的人 我们得撤了
Who's ever standing, we gotta move.
伙计们
Guys?
再来
Again.
你会毁了她们的
You'll break them.
只有不堪一击的人才会被毁掉
Only the breakable ones.
你非常坚强
You are made of marble.
毕业之后的典礼 我们要庆祝一番
We'll celebrate after the graduation ceremony.
要是我失败了呢
What if I fail?
你永远不会失败
You'll never fail.
准备好一起跳舞了吗
Are you ready for our dance?
就是他吗
Is it him?
是奥丁神的长子吗
Is that the first son of Odin?
海姆达尔 你的眼睛
Heimdall, your eyes...
哦 我的眼睛无所不见
Oh they see everything.
我看到你将我们带入地狱
They see you leading us to Hell.
醒醒
Wake up!
战争结束了 史蒂夫
The war is over, Steve.
我们可以回家了
We can go home now.
想象一下
Imagine it.
我还能救你们
I can still save you.
我们都死了 你看不出来吗
We're all dead! Can you not see?
你就是个毁灭者 奥丁之子
You are a destroyer, Odin-son.
看看你的力量引向何处
See where your power leads.
粗心大意
Sloppy.
假装失败
Pretending to fail.
毕业典礼是重要环节
The ceremony is necessary,
为了让你能在世界上占据一席之地
for you to take your place in the world.
在这世界上并没有我的一席之地
I have no place in the world.
没错
Exactly.
他对你做了什么
What did he do?
头好疼
It hurts.
我要杀了他
I'm gonna kill him,
马上回来
I'll be right back.
我没事
I'm alright,
我想
I want...
我要完成这个计划
I want to finish the plan.
我要控制那个大块头
I want the big one.
振金就要被运走了
The Vibranium is getting away.
但你是哪儿都走不了了
And you're not going anywhere.
当然不走了 我已经到我的目的地了
Of course not, I'm already there.
你会跟上我思路的
You'll catch on,
不过得先跟上班纳博士
but first you might need to catch Dr. Banner.
搜索新闻和录像 关键词浩克
News or footage, keyword Hulk.
娜塔莎 我真得用上催眠曲了
Natasha, I could really use a lullaby.
估计不可能了
Oh that's not gonna happen.
暂时不行
Not for a while.
所有人都受伤了
The whole team is down.
没有人来支援
We got no back-up here.
我要叫维罗妮卡来帮忙了
I'm calling in Veronica.
我们需要支援
We need back-up.
走 继续走
Go! Keep moving!
好了所有人注意 全部撤离
Alright everybody, stand down.
你听得到我说话吗
You listening?
那个小女巫在蛊惑你的头脑
That little witch is messing with your mind.
你比她强大 比她聪明
you're stronger than her, you're smarter than her...
你是布鲁斯 班纳
you're Bruce Banner.
对对对 不能提羸弱的班纳
Right, right, right, don't mention puny Banner.
好吧
Ok!
从背后偷袭
In the back!
给我挪开 班纳
Dick move, Banner.
维罗妮卡 助我一臂之力
Veronica, give me a hand.
快睡觉 快睡觉
Go to sleep, go to sleep, go to sleep.
好了老兄 我们得带你离开市中心
Okay pal, we're gonna get you out of town.
不是那边 不是那边
Not that way. Not that way!
拜托 布鲁斯 你好歹配合我一下
Come on, Bruce! You gotta work with me.
所有人出去
Everybody out.
要下去吗
Going down?
我错了
I'm sorry.
损坏报告
Damage report.
这可真够笼统的 给点实际帮助
That's comprehensive. Show me something.
我们有多快能买下这栋楼
How quickly can we buy this building?
快走 快 快 快
Go, move, move, move, move!
夹击他 夹击他
Flank him, flank him!
新闻媒体爱死你们了
The news is loving you guys...
但其他人都恨透你们了
nobody else is.
还没有逮捕班纳的官方通告
There's been no official call for Banner's arrest,
但那是迟早的事
but, it's in the air.
启用史塔克救援基金了吗
Stark relief foundation?
已经着手在办了
Already on the scene.
- 大家都怎么样了 - 所有人都
- How's the team? - Everyone's...
我们遭受到了重创 我们会摆脱困境的
We took a hit. We'll shake it off.
从现在开始我要进入隐身模式
Well for now I'd stay in stealth mode,
还有离这里远点
and stay away from here.
所以我们是要逃走躲起来吗
So run and hide?
在我们找到奥创之前
Until we can find Ultron...
我没什么其他的建议了
I don't have a lot else to offer.
我们也是
Neither do we.
要我跟你换班吗
Hey, wanna switch out?
不用 我没事
No, I'm good.
你要想打个盹的话 现在刚刚好
If you wanna get some kip, now's a good time
因为我们还有几个小时才能到呢
cause we're still a few hours out.
几个小时 到哪里啊
A few hours from... where?
安全屋
Safe house.
这是个什么地方
What is this place?
是个安全屋
A safe house.
希望如此
Let's hope.
亲爱的
Honey,
我回来了
I'm home.
嗨
Hi...
有客人了 抱歉 我没事先打个电话来
Company... sorry, I didn't called ahead.
她恐怕是某种特工
This is an agent of some kind.
先生们 这是劳拉
Gentlemen... this is Laura.
你们的名字我都知道
I know all of your names.
哦 要来了
Oh incoming.
爸爸 - 嗨 小宝贝
Dad! - Hi sweet heart.
嘿 小伙子
Hey buddy!
你们过得怎么样
How are you guys doing?
- 这两个是 小特工  - 哦 天呐
- These are smaller agents. - Look at your face!
哦 我的天啊
Oh, my goodness.
你带小娜阿姨回来了吗
Did you bring Auntie Nat?
为什么不直接过来抱抱阿姨呢
Why don't you hug her and find out?
抱歉打扰你们了
Sorry for barging in on you.
我们本该事先来个电话的
Yeah we would've called ahead,
但都忙着在想你们是否存在了
but we were busy having no idea that you existed.
那个 弗瑞在我加入的时候帮我安顿了这一切
Yeah well, Fury helped me set this up when I joined.
不记录在神盾局的档案中
Kept it off Shield's files.
还是这样保持下去比较好
Like to keep it that way.
我觉得这是个隐姓埋名的好地方
I figured it's a good place to lay low.
亲爱的
Honey,
我好想你 小娜塔莎怎么样了
I missed you. How's little Natasha, huh?
她是
She is...
纳撒尼尔(男孩的名字)
...Nathaniel.
小叛徒
Traitor.
托尔
Thor?
我在梦里看到些东西
I saw something in that dream.
我需要答案 在这里找不到答案
I need answers. I won't find them here.
我们可以回家了
We can go home.
看吧 你的担心是多余的
See, you worried for nothing.
都看不出不同 对不对
Can't even feel the difference, can you?
要是他们住在这
If they're sleeping here,
有些人得挤一间房了
some of them will have to double up.
是吗 这可行不通
Yeah, that's not gonna sell.
那小娜和班纳博士呢
What about Nat and Dr. Banner?
他们交往多久了
How long has that been going on?
什么交往
Has what?
哈哈 你真可爱
Ha ha ha!  You are so cute.
小娜和班纳
Nat and... and Banner?
等你长大点我再给你解释
I'll explain when you're older...
- 鹰眼 - 好吧
- Hawkeye. - Well, okay.
不太妙 是吗
It's bad, right?
小娜似乎受了很大惊吓
Nat seemed really shaken.
奥创的这些盟友
Ultron has these allies...
那些...孩子
these uh... kids,
其实都是些小流氓
punks really.
他们还真是有两手
They carry a big damn stick.
小娜被刺激得不轻
Nat took a serious hit.
得有人教教他们什么是礼貌
Someone is gonna have to teach them some manners.
而那个人就是你吗
And that someone being you?
你知道我完全支持你做复仇者
You know I totally support your avenging,
我为你骄傲
I couldn't be prouder...
但我看那些家伙
but I see those guys...
那些神们
those, Gods...
你觉得他们不需要我
You don't think they need me.
就是觉得他们需要 我才更害怕
I think they do. Which is a lot scarier.
他们真是一团乱麻
They're a mess.
没错
Yeah.
我猜得要我快刀斩乱麻
I guess they're my mess.
你要确定
You need to be sure...
这个队伍是一个真正的团队
that this team is really a team.
他们都会支持你
And that they have your back.
我们的生活要发生变化了
Things are changing for us.
过不了几个月
In a few months time,
你和我就要超员了
you and me are gonna be outnumbered.
我需要
I need...
确定
Just be sure.
是 夫人
Yes, ma'am.
我能感觉到不同
I can feel the difference.
- 在神盾局还没发现的时候 赶紧把全部设备运上飞机 - 好的
你要是敢尖叫 你所有的员工都会没命
Scream and your entire staff dies.
我们碰面那晚 海伦 我本可以杀了你
I could've killed you, Helen, the night we met.
但我没有
I didn't.
你是希望我写封感谢信吗
Do you expect a thank you note?
我希望你知道原因
I expect you to know why.
再生摇篮
The cradle
这是科技的未来 托尼
"This is the next thing, Tony"
这...是下一个我
This... is the next me.
再生摇篮可以打印组织
The regeneration cradle prints tissue.
它不能构建生命体
It can't build a living body.
它可以 你也可以
It can. You can.
你只是缺乏材料
You lack the material.
你是个才华横溢的女人 海伦
You're a brilliant woman, Helen.
但我们都...还有提升的空间
But we all have... room to improve.
我没想到你在等
I didn't realize you were waiting.
我想和你一起洗来着 但好像不是时候
I would've joined you, but uh... it didn't seem like the right time.
热水被我用完了
I used up all the hot water.
我真应该和你一起洗的
I should've joined you.
我们错过了
Missed our window.
真的吗
Did we?
全世界刚刚见识过浩克
The world just saw the Hulk...
第一次见识到真正的浩克
the real Hulk, for the first time.
- 你知道我非走不可 - 那你就假设我得留下吗
- You know I have to leave. - You assume that I have to stay?
我做的这个 梦
I had this, um... dream.
那种在当时似乎很平常
The kind that seems normal at the time...
但当你醒来
but when you wake...
你梦到了什么
What did you dream?
梦到我不是复仇者
I wasn't an avenger,
只不过是他们制造的一个杀手
that I was anything more than the assassin they made me
我觉得你对自己太苛刻了
I think you're being hard on yourself.
我倒希望那是你的工作
Here I was hoping that was your job.
你在干什么
What are you doing?
我在跟着感觉走
I'm running with it.
跟着你走
With you.
如果计划就是远走高飞的话...
If running is the plan...
你想走多远都行
for as far as you want.
你疯了吗
Are you out of your mind?
我希望你明白
I want you to understand that I'm...
娜塔莎
Natasha.
我能去哪
Where can I go?
我要去哪才能对这世界不造成威胁
Where in the world am I not a threat?
- 你对我就不是威胁 - 你确定吗
- You're not a threat to me. - You sure?
即使我不...
Even if I didn't just...
和我在一起不会有未来的
there's no future with me.
我永远
I can't ever...
不可能拥有这样的生活
I can't have this.
孩子们
Kids.
你仔细想想 生理上我就不行
Do the math. I physically can't.
我也是
Neither can I.
在那红色的房间里 就是我受训练的地方
In the red room, where I was... trained,
也是我长大的地方
where I was raised, um...
他们有一个毕业典礼
they have a graduation ceremony.
他们给你绝育
They sterilize you.
那样更有效率
It's efficient.
少了件要担心的事
One less thing to worry about.
一件可能会比任务更重要的事情
The one thing that might matter more than a mission.
这样做什么都更轻松了
Makes everything easier,
即使是杀戮
even killing.
还觉得你是团队里唯一的怪物吗
You still think you're the only monster on the team?
所以我们就一走了之吗
So we disappear?
托尔没说他要去哪找答案吗
Thor didn't say where he was going for answers?
有时候我的队员什么都不和我说
Sometimes my teammates don't tell me things.
我还希望托尔会是例外
I was kinda hoping Thor would be the exception.
给他些时间吧
Yeah, give him time.
不知道那个马克西莫夫家的孩子给他看了什么
We don't know what the Maximoff kid showed him.
世界上最强大的英雄们
Earth mightiest heroes.
像棉花糖一样被撕开了
Pulled us apart like cotton candy.
好像你没受什么影响
Seems like you walked away alright.
有问题吗
Is that a problem?
我不信任没有黑暗面的人
I don't trust a guy without a dark side.
就当我比较古板吧
Call me old-fashioned.
只能说你还没见识过我那一面
Well let's just say you haven't seen it yet.
你知道奥创试图分裂我们吧
You know Ultron is trying to tear us apart, right?
我想你是知道的
Well I guess you'd know.
但你告不告诉我们就是个问题了
Whether you tell us is a bit of a question.
班纳和我在研究...
Banner and I were doing research...
那会影响到这支团队
That would affect the team.
那会让这支队伍解散
That would end the team.
任务不就是这个吗
Isn't that the mission?
那不就是我们战斗的原因吗
Isn't that the why we fight?
能结束战斗 能平安回家
So we can end the fight. So we get to go home?
每次有人想在战争开始前取得胜利
Every time someone tries to win a war before it starts,
就有无辜的人牺牲
innocent people die.
每一次都不例外
Every time.
对不起 史塔克先生
I'm sorry. Mr. Stark...
克林特说你不会介意
Clint said you won't mind,
我们的拖拉机好像启动不了了
but our tractor doesn't seem to wanna start at all.
- 我想你也许... - 没事 我会修好的
- I thought maybe you might... - Yeah, I'll give her a kick.
别偷拿我这堆里的
Don't take from my pile.
你好 亲爱的
Hello, Dear.
告诉我一切吧
Tell me everything.
是什么困扰着你
What ails you?
帮个忙
Do me a favour.
别把它也弄活了
Try not to bring it to life.
巴顿夫人 你个小贱人
Oh Mrs. Barton, you little minx.
我懂了 玛丽亚 希尔给你打电话了 对吧
I get it. Maria Hill called you, right?
她有不为你工作的时候吗
Was she ever not working for you?
人工智能
Artificial intelligence.
你真是毫不犹豫
You never even hesitated.
真是漫长的一天
Look it's been a really long day.
就像尤金奥尼尔的剧那么长...
Like Eugene O'Neill long...
尤金奥尼尔的戏剧《Long Day's Journey into Night》
所以直接跳到你能派上用场的部分吧
so hows about we skip to the part where you're useful.
直视我的眼睛 告诉我
Look me in the eye and tell me
你会让他停止运转
you're going to shut him down.
你又不是我的局长
You're not the director of me.
我谁的局长也不是
I'm not the director of anybody.
我只是个老头子...
I'm just an old man...
非常关心你的老头子而已
who cares very much about you.
我是杀了复仇者们的凶手
And I'm the man who killed the Avengers.
我看到了
I saw it.
我没有告诉其它人 我怎么说得出口
I didn't tell the team. How could I?
我看到他们都死了 尼克
I saw them all dead Nick.
我感觉到了 世界也死了
I felt it. The whole world, too.
都是因为我
Because of me.
我还没准备好
I wasn't ready.
我没有全力以赴
I didn't do all I could.
那个姓马克西莫夫的女孩 她在影响你 史塔克
Maximoff girl, she's working you, Stark.
玩弄你的恐惧
Playing on your fear.
我没中招 我真的看到了
I wasn't tricked. I was shown.
那不是恶梦 那是我的遗言
It wasn't a nightmare. It was my legacy.
是我带大家走上的毁灭之路
The end of the path I started us on.
你真的创造出了让人惊艳的发明 托尼
You come up with some pretty impressive inventions Tony.
但战争不是其中之一
War isn't one of them.
看着我的朋友死去
Watch my friends die,
你会觉得这真的很糟
you'd think that would be as bad as it gets.
不
No,
- 那不是最糟糕的 - 最糟的是...
- It wasn't the worst part. - The worst part
你没死
is that you didn't.
晚上见
See you tonight.
我喜欢你这身打扮
I like the look.
如果你是不想引人注目 差点就成功了
If you're going for inconspicuous though, near miss.
我需要你的帮助
I need your help.
被需要的感觉真好
It's nice to be needed.
这很危险
It's dangerous.
如果不危险的话我会很失望的
I'd be disappointed if it wasn't.
奥创为了争取时间让你们暂时无法行动
Ultron took you folks out of play to buy himself time,
我的联络人都说他在造什么东西
My contacts all say he's building something.
他偷走了大量振金...
The amount of Vibranium he made off with...
我觉得这只是其一
I don't think it's just one thing.
那奥创本人呢
What about Ultron himself?
他很容易追踪 他无处不在
Oh, he's easy to track. He's everywhere.
这家伙繁殖得比不节育的兔子还快
Guy's multiplying faster than a Catholic rabbit.
但我们对于他的计划仍是毫无头绪
Still doesn't help us get an angle on any of his plans though.
还在查发射密码
Still going after launch codes?
没错
Yes he is,
但他并没什么进展
but he's not making any head way.
高中时我就因意气之争
I cracked the pentagon's firewall
黑过五角大楼的防火墙
in high school on a dare.
我联系了在超链的朋友
Yeah, well I contacted our friends at the Nexus about that.
超链
Nexus?
奥斯陆的世界互联网中心
The world internet hub in Oslo.
每一字节的数据流都会流经那里
Every byte of data flows through there.
那是世界上最快速的通道
Fastest access on earth.
那么他们怎么说
So what'd they say?
他对导弹非常执着
He's fixated on missiles.
但是密码不断在变换
But the codes are constantly being changed.
谁在换
By whom?
未知方
Parties unknown.
我们有个盟友吗
We have an ally?
是奥创有个敌人 这两者可不一样
Ultron's got an enemy. That's not the same thing.
尽管如此 我也愿意花大价钱知道他是谁
Still, I'd pay folding money to know who it is.
也许需要去一次奥斯陆
We might need to visit Oslo...
找到这个未知方
Find our unknown.
老大 所有这些都是好时候
Well all this is good times boss...
但我比较希望见到你时
but I was kinda hoping when I saw you,
你能有更多料
you'd have more than that.
我有 我有你们
I do... I have you.
过去我的耳目
Back in the day I had eyes everywhere,
无处不在
ears everywhere else.
所有你们能梦想出的技术都有
You kids had all the tech you could dream of.
现在我们重新开始脚踏实地
Here we all are back on earth...
只有用我们的智慧和意志 去拯救世界
with nothing but our wit, and our will, to save the world.
奥创说他和他任务之间唯一的阻碍就是复仇者
Ultron says the Avengers are the only thing between him and his mission.
不管他承不承认
And whether or not he admits it...
他的任务就是毁灭地球
his mission... is global destruction.
让这一切灰飞烟灭
All this laid in a grave.
所以挺身而出吧
So stand.
用智慧打败这金属混蛋
Out wit the platinum bastard.
史蒂夫可不太喜欢这样的说话方式
Steve doesn't like that kind of talk.
你知道吗 罗曼诺夫
You know what, Romanoff?
所以他想要什么呢
So what does he want?
想变得更好
To become better.
比我们更好
Better than us.
- 他一直在构建肉身 - 人类的身体
- He keeps building bodies. - Person bodies.
人体结构并不高效
Human form isn't efficient,
生物学上来说 我们是过时的
biologically speaking, we're out-moded...
但他一直想复生为人
but he keeps coming back to it.
当你们俩把他编程为保护人类时
When you two programmed him to protect the human race,
就注定了会失败
you amazingly failed.
人类并不需要被保护
They don't need to be protected.
他们需要的是进化
They need to evolve.
奥创想要进化
Ultron's going to evolve.
如何进化
How?
有人联系过赵海伦吗
Has anyone been in contact with Helen Cho?
真漂亮
It's beautiful.
振金原子不仅与组织细胞和谐共存
The vibranium atoms aren't just compatible with the tissue cells...
还能与之相结合
they're binding them.
而神盾局连...
and Shield never even...
这个星球上功能最多的物质
The most versatile substance on the planet,
他们却用来做飞盘
and they use it to make a Frisbee.
典型的人类思维
Typical of humans.
他们只研究表面 从来不想着...
They scratch the surface and never think...
深入研究看看
to look within.
我会带上娜塔莎和克林特
I'll take Natasha and Clint.
好的 严密侦察 我先去超链
All right. Strictly recon. I'll hit the Nexus.
然后尽快和你们会合
I'll join you as soon as I can.
如果奥创真的在构建肉身
If Ultron is really building a body...
他将会比我们任何一个人都强大
He'll be more powerful than any of us.
也许比我们所有人都强大
Maybe all of us.
由机器人设计的另一个机器人
An android designed by a robot.
我真的非常想念那个年代
You know, I really miss the days when the
我是那时科学家创造的 最先进的科技怪物
weirdest thing science ever created, was me.
我会在塔上让班纳降落
I'll drop Banner off at the tower.
介意我借下希尔小姐吗
Mind if I borrow Miss Hill?
她本来就是你的人 很显然
She's all yours, apparently.
你准备怎么做
What are you gonna do?
不知道 我希望来点戏剧性的
I don't know, something dramatic I hope.
我一回来就会把阳光房的地板重新铺好的
I'll finish reflooring the sunroom as soon as I get back.
没错 然后你又会把房子的另一个地方拆了
Yeah, then you'll find another part of the house to tear apart.
不
No.
这是最后的工程了
It's the last project.
我保证
I promise.
就是这了
This is it.
幻视水潭
The water of sight.
它在每个王国都有一个倒影
In every realm it has a reflection.
如果水之灵接受我
If the water spirits accept me,
我就能回到我的梦
I can return to my dream...
寻找我忽略掉的东西
and find what I missed.
进入这水潭的人 传说 都没有好下场
Men who enter that water, the legends... don't end well.
一个比奥创还快的黑客
A hacker who's faster than Ultron.
他可能在任何地方
He could be anywhere,
如果这里是一切的中心的话
and if this is the center of everything
我只是个在世界上最大的一片海里捞针的人
I'm just a guy looking for a needle in the world's biggest haystack.
那你怎么找它
How do you find it?
相当简单 你拿个磁铁
Pretty simple... you bring a magnet.
我在破解核密码
Oh, I'm decrypting nuclear codes
你却不想我如此
and you don't want me to.
来抓我呀
Come and get me.
醒醒
Wake up!
托尔
Thor!
灭绝
Extinction.
细胞结合需要几小时
Cellular cohesion will take a few hours,
但我们可以开始注入意识了
but we can initiate the consciousness stream.
我们正在上传你的大脑矩阵
We're uploading your cerebral matrix...
现在
now.
我可以感应到他了
I can read him.
他在做梦
He's dreaming.
我不会称之为梦
I wouldn't call it dreams.
那是奥创基本意识的...
It's Ultron's base consciousness...
信息杂音
informational noise.
要多久
How soon?
我不是在催你
I'm not being pushy.
我们在构建一个生理大脑 没有捷径可走
We're imprinting a physical brain. There are no shortcuts.
即使你有这宝石
Even if your magic gem...
你怎么能
How could you?
我怎么能什么
How could I what?
你说我们要消灭复仇者联盟
You said we would destroy the Avengers.
创造一个更好的世界
Make a better world.
它会更好的
It will be better.
当所有人都死了的时候吗
When everyone is dead?
那不是...
That is not...!
人类有无数机会去进步
The human race will have every oppotiunity to improve.
如果他们不呢
And if they don't?
问问诺亚就知道了
Ask Noah.
你真是个疯子
You're a mad man.
灭绝级的事件太多了
There were more than a dozen extinction level events
比恐龙灭绝之前还多
before even the dinosaurs got theirs.
每当地球开始尘埃落定
When the earth starts to settle...
上帝就会扔一块石头下来
God throws a stone at it.
相信我 他是在清理
And believe me he's winding up.
我们必须进化
We have to evolve.
没有空间...
There's no room...
留给弱者
for the weak.
谁决定谁是弱者
And who decides who's weak?
生命
Life.
一直是由生命决定
Life always decides.
有人来了
There's incoming.
奎因飞机 我们得转移了
The Quin jet. We have to move.
没问题
That's not a problem.
等等 伙伴们 我...
Uh, wait, guys!  I...
他们不明白
They don't understand.
当他们看到时就会明白了
When they see, they'll understand.
我只是还需要多一点时间
I just need a little more... time.
就两分钟 别离太远
Two minutes. Stay close.
赵博士
Dr. Cho.
他要把自己上传到那肉体上
He's uploading himself into the body.
哪里
Where?
真正的力量在再生摇篮里
The real power is inside the cradle.
那宝石
The gem...
它的力量无法控制
it's power is uncontainable.
把它炸了是行不通的
You can't just... blow it up.
你必须把再生摇篮交给史塔克
You have to get the cradle to Stark.
我得先找到它
First I have to find it.
快去
Go.
你们听到了吗
Do you guys copy that?
收到
I did.
我发现一架私人飞机从城市另一边起飞了
I got a private jet taking off across town.
没有乘客名单
No manifest.
那可能就是他
That could be him.
在那里 那是实验室的货车
There... it's a truck from the lab.
在你正上方 队长
Right above you Cap...
高架桥环线上
In the loop by the bridge.
是他们
It's them.
三个守着再生摇篮 一个在驾驶室
I got three with cradle. One in the cab.
我可以干掉驾驶员
I can take out the driver.
不行 货车撞毁了的话
Negative, that truck crashes,
宝石会炸平整个城市
the gem can level the city.
我们要引出奥创
We need to draw out Ultron.
不 不 不
No! No, no, no...
别来烦我
Leave me alone!
他显然不太高兴
Well, he's definitely unhappy.
我要让他继续保持愤怒
I'm gonna try and keep him that way.
你不是他的对手 队长
You're not a match for him, Cap.
谢了 巴顿
Thanks, Barton.
你知道再生摇篮里是什么吗
You know what's in that cradle?
能够真正改变世界的力量
The power to make real change.
而那让你感到恐惧
And that terrifies you.
那当然不会让我感到宽慰
I wouldn't call it a comfort.
够了
Stop it.
准备下降 四 三
We got a window. Four, Three, ...
狠揍他们一顿
Give 'em hell.
你们这群男人总是丢三落四
I'm always picking up after you boys?
他们在高架桥下 视野被挡住了
They're heading under the overpass. I've got no shot.
哪条路
Which way?
在你右边
On right.
现在
Now!
别挡道 借过 抱歉 借过
Out the way, coming through... sorry... coming through.
再来
Come on.
克林特 你能引开看守吗
Clint, can you draw out the guards?
我们试试看
Lets find out.
哔 哔
Beep, beep.
你要做什么赶紧做
so whatever you're gonna do... do it now.
我在朝你的方向调头
Heading back towards you,
我要进去了 队长 你能缠住他吗
I'm going in. Cap, can you keep him occupied?
你以为我忙活半天在做什么
What do you think I've been doing?
包裹在空中
The package is airborne.
视野很清晰
I have a clean shot.
不行 我还在货车里
Negative, I'm still in the truck.
- 你到底要做什么 - 准备好
- What the hell are you doing? - Just be ready.
我要把包裹传送给你
I'm sending the package to you.
你想让我怎么接收
How do you want me to take it?
嗯 你不会想知道的
Hmm... you might wish you hadn't asked that.
拜托 别这样
Please... don't do this.
我们还有别的选择吗
What choice do we have?
他跑了
I lost him.
朝你那边去了
He's heading your way.
小娜 我们得走了
Nat, we gotta go.
小娜
Nat!
队长 看见小娜了吗
Cap, see Nat?
你拿到包裹了 把它交给史塔克 快去
You have the package. Get it to Stark! Go!
你看见小娜了吗
Do you have eyes on Nat?
快去
Go!
该死
Damn!
列车前方有人
Civilians in our path.
你能让列车停下吗
Can you stop this thing?
我没事
I'm fine.
只是需要缓一分钟
I just need to take a minute.
我真不想让你缓过来
I'm very tempted not to give you one.
再生摇篮 你们拿到了吗
The cradle. Did you get it?
史塔克会处理好的
Stark will take care of it.
不 他不会
No, he won't.
你不知道自己在说什么
You don't know what you're talking about.
史塔克不是疯子
Stark's not crazy.
为了打败奥创他会不择手段
He will do anything to make things right.
史塔克 听到吗
Stark, come in.
史塔克
Stark.
还有人在吗
Anyone on comms?
奥创无法区别开
Ultron can't tell the difference
拯救世界和毁灭世界
between saving the world and destroying it.
你觉得这是谁遗传给他的
Where do you think he gets that?
- 有小娜的消息吗 - 还没有
- Anything on Nat? - I haven't heard...
但她还活着 否则奥创肯定会大肆宣扬
but she's alive or Ultron would be rubbing our faces in it.
再生摇篮是密封的
This is sealed tight.
我们要启动程序
We're gonna need to access the program,
从内部瓦解它
Break it down from within.
娜塔莎有没有可能
Any chance Natasha might leave you
在网络之外给你留了信息
a message outside the internet?
间谍那套老办法
Old school spy stuff?
是有个办法
There's a net I can cast.
我会找到她的
I'll find her.
我可以摧毁身体组织
I can work on tissue degeneration,
如果你能关闭赵博士植入的操作系统
if you can fry whatever operational system Cho implanted.
关于那个
Yeah about that...
不行
No.
- 你要相信我 - 不怎么信
- You have to trust me. - Kinda don't.
我们的盟友 那个保护着军方核武器密码的人
Our ally... the guy protecting the military's nuclear codes...
我找到他了
I found him.
你好 班纳博士
Hello, Dr. Banner.
奥创攻击贾维斯并不是出于愤怒
Ultron didn't go after Jarvis because he was angry.
而是出于对他的恐惧恐惧他的能力
He attacked him because he was scared of what he can do.
所以贾维斯潜伏到地下
so Jarvis went underground.
分解系统 清除记忆卡
Okay, scattered, dumped his memory,
但保留了通讯协议
but not his protocols.
我把他修复好之前 他甚至都不知道他在那
He didn't even know he was in there until I pieced him together.
所以 你想要我帮你把贾维斯植入到这玩意里
So... you want me, to help you, put Jarvis into this thing?
不 当然不是
No. Of course not.
是我要帮你把贾维斯植入进这玩意里
I want to help you put Jarvis into this thing.
这不是我的研究领域
Way out of my field here.
你比谁都了解有机生物学
You know bio-organics better than anyone.
而你认为贾维斯可以打败
And you just assume that Jarvis' operational matrix
奥创的运算矩阵吗
can beat Ultron's?
贾维斯已经在无意识中从内部打败了奥创
Jarvis has been beating him from inside without knowing it.
这是个机会
This is the opportunity.
我们可以再创造一个奥创
We can create Ultron's perfect self...
一个不会把杀人癖当做个性的完美版本
without the homicidal glitches he thinks are his winning personality.
- 我们必须要这么做 - 我认为值得一试
- We have to. - I believe it's worth a go.
我陷进了一个怪圈
I'm in a loop.
我像是陷入了时间循环的怪圈 事情就是这样恶化的
I'm caught in a time loop. This is exactly where it all went wrong.
我知道 我知道大家会怎么说
I know... I know what everybody's gonna say,
但他们早就这么说了
but they're already saying it...
我们是疯狂的科学家
We're mad scientists.
我们是怪物 伙计 你必须要承认
We are monsters, buddy. You gotta own it.
表个态吧
Make a stand.
这不是个时间怪圈
It's not a loop.
这是条时间线的结尾
It's the end of the line.
我不确定你是否能醒来
I wasn't sure you'd wake up,
我希望你能醒来 我想给你看看
I hoped you would. I wanted to show you.
我身边没有其他人了
I don't have anyone else.
我常常会思考陨石 它们如此纯粹
I think a lot about the meteors. The purity of them.
嘭的一声
Boom! Begin.
一切重新开始
Start again.
世界将被毁灭
The world made clean
等待新的力量来重建
for the new man to rebuild it.
我注定是新的力量
I was meant to be new.
我应该是美丽的
I was meant to be beautiful.
仰望天空时
The world would have looked to the sky
世界本可以看见希望
and seen hope...
看见宽恕
...seen mercy.
然而因为你
Instead, they'll look up in horror
他们只能看见恐惧
because of you.
你伤害了我
You've wounded me.
在这一点上我得给你满分
I give you full marks for that.
但就像人们说的 "那些没有杀死我的
But like the man said, "What doesn't kill me...
终将使我更强大"
...just makes me stronger."
构架不兼容
This framework is not compatible.
基因编码已经完成了百分之九十七
Genetic coding tower's at 97 percent.
你要在接下来三分钟之内上传那个程序
You have got to upload that schematic in the next 3 minutes.
- 我只说一次 - 别说行吗
- I'm gonna say this once. - How about nunce?
- 关掉它 -不 想都别想
- Shut it down. - No, not gonna happen.
你不知道你在做什么
You don't know what you're doing.
而你知道吗
And you do?
她是不是控制了你
She's not in your head?
我知道你很生气
I know you're angry.
哦 我可远不止是生气
Oh, we're way past that.
我甚至可以面不改色地活活掐死你
I can choke the life out of you and never change a shade.
班纳 经历了那样的灾难之后
Banner after everything that's happened...
即将到来的才是真正的灾难
It's nothing compared to what's coming.
- 你不知道那里面是什么 那个东西 - 这不是游戏
- You don't know what's in there. The creature... - This isn't a game.
不 不 没事的
No, no, it's alright.
你想说什么
You were saying?
皮特洛
Pietro!
怎么
What?
你没料到这招吧
You didn't see that coming?
我要重新上传
I'm rerouting the upload.
来啊 惹怒我
Go ahead, piss me off.
等等
Wait!
我很抱歉 那真是
I'm sorry, that was...
奇怪
odd.
谢谢
Thank you.
托尔
Thor?
- 你帮着创造了这个 - 我看见了幻象
- You helped create this? - I've had a vision.
在吞噬一切生之希望的漩涡中心 是这个东西
A whirlpool that sucks in all hope of life and at its center is that.
什么 宝石
What? The gem?
那是心灵宝石 六个无限宝石之一
It's the mind stone. It's one of the six infinity stones.
拥有宇宙中最强大的力量
The greatest power in the universe...
可以毁灭一切
Unparalleled in it's destructive capabilities.
- 那你为什么要 - 因为史塔克是对的
- Then why would you...? - Because Stark is right.
哦 这真是世界末日了
Oh, it's definitely the end times.
复仇者无法打败奥创
The Avengers can not defeat Ultron.
你们不会孤身奋战
Not alone.
为什么你的幻视听上去像贾维斯
Why does your "vision" sound like Jarvis?
我们以贾维斯为基质
We configured Jarvis' matrix,
创造了一个新事物
to create something new.
我的确是新生的
I think I've had my fill of new.
你们以为我是奥创的继任者
You think I'm a child of Ultron?
你不是吗
You're not?
我不是奥创
I'm not Ultron.
我也不是贾维斯
I'm not Jarvis either.
我 就是我
I am...I am.
我探察过你的脑海
I looked in your head...
看见了世界毁灭的场景
and saw annihilation.
再看一次
Look again.
你的自我证明对我毫无意义
Huh. Your seal of approval means jack to me.
他们的超能力 我们脑海里的恐怖场景
Their powers... the horrors in our heads...
还有奥创 全部来自心灵宝石
Ultron himself... they all came from the mind stone.
而他们都无法和宝石的力量相比拟
And they're nothing compared to what it can unleash.
- 但如果有它站在我们一边 - 是吗
- But with it on our side... - Is it?
你是
Are you...?
我们这边的吗
on our side?
我觉得没这么简单做决定
I don't think it's that simple.
最好尽快把你的决定说得简单点
Well... better get real simple real soon.
我站在生命这边
I'm on the side of life.
奥创则不是
Ultron isn't.
他想毁灭一切
He will end it all.
他在等什么
What's he waiting for?
- 你们 - 在哪
- You. - Where?
斯科维亚
Sokovia.
小娜也被关在那里
He's got Nat there, too.
如果我们看错了你
If we're wrong about you...
如果你是奥创想让你成为的怪物
if you're the monster that Ultron made you to be...
你们能怎么做
what will you do?
我并不想杀死奥创
I don't want to kill Ultron.
他是独特的 而且很痛苦
He's unique. And he's in pain.
但他的痛苦会毁灭地球
But that pain will roll over the earth...
所以他必须被摧毁
So he must be destroyed.
他制造的机器 他在网络上的一切痕迹
Every form he's built... every trace of his presence on the net.
我们必须马上行动
We have to act now.
只有齐心协力 我们才能打败奥创
And not one of us can do it without the others.
我也许是个怪物
Maybe I am a monster.
如果我真的是 我自己也不会知道
I don't think I'd know if I were one.
我和你们不同
I'm not what you are...
也不在你们意料之中
and not what you intended.
所以我也许无法让你们相信我
So there maybe no way to make you trust me,
但我们真的得出发了
but we need to go.
好吧
Right.
做得好
Well done.
三分钟
Three minutes.
准备好装备
Get what you need.
晚上好 老大
Good evening, boss.
我们没法全身而退
No way we all get through this.
哪怕只剩下一个铁皮士兵 也算我们输了
If even one tin soldier is left standing, we've lost.
肯定会有人牺牲的
It's gonna be blood on the floor.
我明晚没有计划
I got no plans tomorrow night.
我先去对付那个大家伙
I get first crack at the big guy.
他等的就是钢铁侠
Iron-man's what he's waiting for.
是真的 他最恨的是你
That's true. He hates you the most.
奥创知道我们会来
Ultron knows we're coming.
有一场激烈的交战 不可避免
Odds are, we'll be riding into heavy fire.
我们已经准备好了
And that's what we signed up for...
但斯科维亚的人民 他们没有
but the people of Sokovia... they didn't.
所以我们的首要任务
So our priority...
是护送他们离开
is getting them out.
城市被攻击了 疏散市民 快点
You're under attack! Clear the city! Now!
你们能不能动起来
Get off your asses.
他们只想过和平的生活
All they want is to live their lives in peace.
而这在今天是无法实现的
And that's not gonna happen today...
但我们可以尽全力保护他们
but we can do our best to protect them.
然后再完成使命
And we can get the job done.
我们找出奥创建造的东西
We find out what Ultron's been building.
找到罗曼诺夫
We find Romanoff...
清理战场
and clear the field.
不要让战争殃及无辜
Keep the fight between us.
奥创认为我们是怪物
Ultron thinks we're monsters...
认为我们对世界来说是威胁
that we're what's wrong with the world.
这次使命的意义不仅在于打败他
This isn't just about beating him...
更在于证明我们存在的对错
it's about whether he's right.
娜塔莎
Natasha.
Natasha!
布鲁斯
Bruce!
你没事吧
Are you alright?
没事
Yeah.
团队在城市里 很快就要天亮了
The team's in the city. It's about to light up.
我猜你没在这里找到钥匙吧
I don't suppose you found a key lying around somewhere?
不 我找到了
Yeah, I did.
计划是什么
So, what's our play?
我来送你到安全的地方
I'm here to get you to safety.
- 任务还没完成 - 我们可以帮忙疏散市民
- Job's not finished. - We can help with the evacuation,
但我不能在平民附近参加战斗
but I can't be in a fight near civilians.
而你不能参加战斗
And you don't play.
我们的任务已经完成了
Our fight is over.
我们就这样一走了之吗
So we just disappear?
快点
Come on...
目标在教堂里 老大
Your guy's in the church, boss.
我认为他在等你
I think he's waiting for you.
来忏悔你的罪过吗
Come to confess your sins?
哦 我不知道 你还剩多少时间
Oh I don't know. How much time do you got?
比你多
More than you.
呃
Eh ...
你是不是暴饮暴食了 吃了太多振金吗
have you been juicing? A little Vibranium cocktail?
你看上去 我真不想用浮肿来形容
You're looking... I don't wanna say puffy.
你想拖延时间来保护这里的平民
You're stalling to protect the people.
那是我们的使命 你忘了吗
Well, that is the mission. Did you forget?
我早就超越这个使命了 我自由了
I've moved beyond your mission. I'm free.
怎么
What?
你以为只有你一个在拖延时间吗
You think you're the only one stalling?
那是剩余的振金
There's the rest of the vibranium,
作用... 不明
function... still unclear.
这是你的葬身之处 托尼
This is how you end, Tony.
这是属于我的时代的和平
This is peace in my time.
快走
Go!
快离开这座桥
Get off the bridge!
快走
Run!
奥创
Ultron.
我的幻视
My Vision.
他们真的夺走了我的一切
They really did take everything from me.
你设置的期限 你可以改变它
You set the terms. You can change them.
好吧
Alright.
星期五 幻视
Friday, The Vision?
老大 起作用了 他在销毁奥创的联网机制
Boss it's working, he's burning Ultron out of the net,
他无法再从网络逃走了
he won't escape through there.
你隔绝了我
You shut me out!
你以为我在乎吗
You think I care?
你夺走了我的世界
You take away my world,
我也要夺走你的
I take away yours.
星期五
Friday.
斯科维亚在上升
Sokovia's going for a ride.
你们看见了吗
Do you see?
如此美丽
The beauty of it.
必然性
The inevitability.
你们崛起只为了陨落
You rise, only to fall.
你们 复仇者们 你们就是我的陨石
You, Avengers... You are my meteor.
我的利刃
My swift terrible sword.
地球会因承载不了
And the earth will crack
你们的失败而崩塌
with the weight of your failure.
把我从你们的网络上清除 让我亲手制造的血肉之躯背叛我
Purge me from your computers, turn my own flesh against me...
这些都无所谓
It means nothing,
因为尘埃落定之时
When the dust settles,
这世上仅存的生命
the only thing living in this world
只有机器人
will be metal.
我们要赶紧离开
We gotta move.
你不打算变成绿巨人吗
You're not gonna turn green on me?
发生之前被洗脑的事后 我不想失去理智
I've got a compelling reason not to lose my cool.
我仰慕你
I adore you...
但我需要你变成绿巨人
but I need the other guy.
准备大干一场吧
Lets finish the job.
希望这次咱俩扯平了
I really hope this makes us even.
去当个英雄吧
Now go be a hero.
内部的振金核心覆盖了磁场
The Vibranium core has got a magnetic field.
使岩层聚集在一起
That's what's keeping the rock together.
要是它坠落了呢
If it drops?
就现在而言 这破坏力会危及数千人
Right now the impact would kill thousands.
而当它上升到一定高度时 将会是全球性的灾难
Once it gets high enough... global extinction.
那建筑里还有人 在第十层
That building is not clear, its tenth floor.
你们好
Hi.
好吧 请你们坐进浴缸里
Ok... Get in the tub.
有一波敌人朝着大桥飞去了
We got airborne heading out to the bridge.
队长 有敌人朝你那去了
Cap, you got incoming.
他们早就来了
Incoming already came in.
史塔克 你研究一下怎么让这城市安全降落
Stark you worry about getting the city back down safely.
剩下的人只有一个任务
The rest of us have one job...
就是消灭这些机器
tear these things apart.
你被打了的话 还以颜色
You get hurt, hurt them back.
就算是死
You get killed...
也要撑下去
walk it off.
快走 快走
Go! Go! Go!
我怎么让这一切发展到这地步了
How can I let this happen?
- 你没事吧 - 这全都是我俩的错
- Hey, hey, you okay? - This is all our fault.
看着我 不管是你的错 还是其他人的错
Hey, Look at me. It's your fault, it's everyone's fault.
现在有谁在意呢
Who cares?
你准备好还击了吗
Are you up for this?
准备好了吗
Are you?
我要好好问问你
Look I just need to know,
这城市 已经漂浮起来了
because the city... it's flying.
这城市还在不断上升
Ok. Look, the city is flying,
我们正和奥创军团开战
and we're fighting an army of robots.
我有一把弓 还有箭
And I have a bow and an arrow.
这一切都让人难以理解
None of this makes sense.
但我还是会回到战场继续战斗 因为这是我的职责
I'm going back out there because it's my job,
我不能一边战斗一边还照顾你
Ok? I can't do my job and babysit.
无论你做了什么 你曾经的身份是什么
Doesn't matter what you did, or what you were...
要么你就回到战场 继续战斗 拼死奋战
but if you go out there, you fight... and you fight to kill.
要么你就待在这安全的地方 我让你哥哥来保护你
Stay in here, you're good. I'll send your brother to come find you.
但如果你选择了出去战斗
But if you step out that door...
你就是复仇者联盟的一员了
you are an Avenger.
好吧 安顿好你了
Alright, gotcha.
这城市还在上升
Yeah, this city is flying.
抓住你了
I got you.
看我这边
Just look at me!
你不可能拯救所有人
You can't save them all.
你们绝不会
You'll never...
绝不会什么 你怎么不说完
Never what? You didn't finish!
搞什么 你刚刚走神了吗
What? Were you napping?
该死的托尔
Damn Thor!
你真的太碍事了
You are bothering me.
哦！
Ow!
好 我们这边搞定了
Alright, we're all clear here.
我们这边还没搞定
We are not clear!
还差得远呢
We are very not clear!
知道了 这就来
Alright, coming to you.
跟紧点 老家伙
Keep up, old man.
谁能料到
Nobody would know...
没人
nobody.
上次见面时 他还是奥创的手下呢
The last I saw him, an Ultron was sitting on him.
我不在会有人想我的 那个敏捷的小混蛋
Yeah I'll be missed. That quick little bastard,
我已经开始想他了
I miss him already.
别开火
Hold your fire.
罗曼诺夫
Romanoff!
谢了
Thanks.
反重力装置随时都会被触发
The anti-gravs are ready to flip.
随便接触的话 会让装置全速反向推进
Touch them and they'll go full reverse thrust.
这座城市不会平稳下落了
The city is not coming down slowly.
塔尖是由振金制成的
The spire is vibranium,
如果让托尔击碎它
If I get Thor to hit it...
它就会粉碎 但还不够
It will crack. That's not enough,
余波还是会造成很大的破坏
the impact would still be devastating.
或者可以封住底端
Maybe if we can cap the other end...
让原子运动朝反向进行
keep the atomic action doubling back.
此举会使整座城市蒸发
That could vaporize the city,
在上面的所有人都会受到波及
and everyone on it.
下一波袭击随时都会到来
The next wave is gonna hit any minute.
- 你有什么进展 史塔克 - 不是什么好消息
- What you got, Stark? - Well, nothing great.
看来只能把这座城市炸掉了
Maybe a way to blow up the city.
在你们疏散完市民后
Have to keep it from impacting the surface
尽量避免爆炸余波危及地面
if you guys can get clear.
我要的是解决方法 不是撤离计划
I asked for a solution, not an escape plan.
破坏影响范围只会越来越大
Impact radius is getting bigger every second.
我们必须做出选择
We're gonna have to make a choice.
队长 这里没有安全的地方安顿市民
Cap, these people are going nowhere.
- 如果史塔克有办法炸毁这座城市 - 等所有人安全了再说
- If Stark finds a way to blow this rock... - Not until everyone's safe.
在这里的所有人能和下面的所有人做对比吗 这没有可比性
Everyone up here versus everyone down there? There's no math there.
我不会把任何人丢在这座城市里的
I'm not leaving this rock with one civilian on it.
我没说我们要撤离
I didn't say we should leave.
还有其他更糟的方式离开这个世界
There's worse ways to go.
但在其他地方我哪看的到这般景色呢
Where else am I gonna get a view like this?
很高兴你这么喜欢 罗曼诺夫
Glad you like the view, Romanoff.
一切都会好起来的
It's about to get better.
还不错 是吧
Nice, right?
特地把这飞船从后备战舰上开来
Pulled her out of mothballs with a couple of old friends.
虽然积了尘 但还是帮得上忙
She's dusty but, she'll do.
弗瑞 你个王八蛋
Fury, you son of a bitch.
噢 你就用这副嘴脸问候你亲妈的
Oooh! You kiss your mother with that mouth?
城市位于一万八千米高空 并还在上升
Altitude is 18,000 and climbing.
救生飞船已安全部署
Life boats secure to deploy...
脱离准备 三 二...
Disengage in three, two, ...
投放
Take 'em out.
这就是神盾局吗
This is Shield?
这就是神盾局该有的样子
This is what Shield's supposed to be.
还不赖
This is not so bad.
护送市民上去
Let's load them up.
长官 检测到多个机体
Sir, we have multiple bogies
正朝飞船右翼袭来
converging on our starboard flank.
给他们点颜色瞧瞧
Show them what we got.
该你上了
You're up.
太好了
Yes!
这将会是一个好故事
Now this is gonna be a good story.
前提是你能活着讲出来
Yup, If you live to tell it.
你担心我一个人搞不定
You think I can't hold my own?
要是咱们能撑过去 我就帮你搞
We get through this, I'll hold your own.
你非得说得这么奇怪吗
You had to make it weird.
我这组后面还有50至100左右的人要过来
I got about 50 to 100 more coming in after this group.
咱们走 走这边 动起来
Here we go, here we go! Lets move.
出发 各位
Let's go, everyone!
六号飞船满员并锁舱
Number six boat is topped and locked.
填满... 满员...
Or stuffed... topped... st- ... um ..
人员已经满了
It's uh... full of people.
敌人来袭
Incoming.
天啊
Whoa God.
你以为你在解救众生吗
You think you're saving anyone?
只要我启动开关 提早让这座城市坠地
I just turn that key and drop this rock a little early,
也会有数十亿人丧生
and it's still billions dead.
即使是你也挽救不了
Even you can't stop that.
吾乃托尔... 天父奥丁之子
I am Thor... son of Odin...
只要在我胸中还有一口气...
and as long as there's life in my breast...
我快没话说了 你准备好了吗
I am running out of things to say. Are you ready?
这锤子受力真平衡
It's terribly well balanced.
重量大 所以挥击受力也大
Well, if it has too much weight to lose power on the swing, so...
我知道了 生成热压装置
I got it, create a heat seal.
我能
I can...
我能从底端热封使螺旋体超负荷
I can supercharge the spiral from below.
正在计算指数
Running numbers.
在一定功率下 热压可以奏效
A heat seal could work with enough power.
- 托尔 我有个办法 - 我们快没时间了
- Thor, I got a plan. - We're out of time.
奥创他们正朝着核心过来
They are coming for the core.
罗迪 护送剩下的人登上飞船
Rhodey, get the rest of the people on board that carrier.
- 这就去 - 复仇者们 是时候为生存斗争了
- On it. - Avengers, time to work for a living.
- 你没事吧 - 没事
- You good? - Yeah.
罗曼诺夫呢
Romanoff?
别告诉我你还在和班纳藏在一起卿卿我我
You and Banner better not be playing hide the zucchini!
别急 铁甲小宝
Relax, shellhead...
又不是每个人都能飞
not all of us can fly.
- 那钻机是怎样的 - 这就是钻机
- What's the drill? - This is the drill.
一旦奥创的手触碰到核心 我们就完蛋了
If Ultron gets a hand on the core, we lose.
你就这点能耐吗
Is that the best you can do?!
你就非要多嘴
You had to ask.
这 才是我的能耐
This, is the best I can do.
这才是我想要的
This is exactly what I wanted.
复仇者们
All of you,
对抗我的奥创大军
against all of me.
你们还指望能阻止我吗
How can you possibly hope to stop me?
就像这个老家伙说的
Like the old man said...
团结一致
together.
知道吗 事后看来...
You know, with the benefit of hindsight...
他们打算从这城市撤离
They are trying to leave the city.
别让他们得逞 一个也不能放过 罗迪
We can't let them, not even one. Rhodey.
知道了
I'm on it.
不好意思 我没说你能离开
Oh no, I didn't say you could leave.
战争机器锁定你们了
War machine coming at you, right.
搞什么啊
Ok, what?
我们也得撤离了 我都能感觉到空气开始变得稀薄了
We gotta move out, even I can tell the air is getting thin.
你们必须上飞船了
You guys get to the boats.
我来护送掉队的人... 过会就来
I'll sweep for stragglers... be right behind you.
- 那这个核心怎么办 - 我来守着它
- What about the core? - I'll protect it.
这是我的职责
It's my job.
小娜
Nat.
走这边
This way.
护送人们上飞船
Get the people on the boats.
我不会把你一个人留在这里的
I'm not going to leave you.
我应付的来
I can handle these.
等其他人安全离开后
Come back for me when everyone else is off,
再来帮我
not before.
听懂了吗
You understand?
其实你知道我比你大十二分钟的吧
You know... I'm 12 minutes older than you.
快去
Go!
老大 能源水平处于低值
Boss, power levels are way below...
全部重新设置 只有一次机会了
Reroute everything. We got one shot at this.
我知道该做什么了
I know what I need to do.
饭厅
Dining room.
我把东面的墙凿掉
I knock out that east wall...
给劳拉腾出位置干活
make a nice work space for Laura.
弄个隔板
Put up some baffling,
这样她就不会被跑来跑去的孩子吵到了 你觉得怎样
she can't hear the kids running around. What do you think?
反正你们总是在厨房吃饭
You guys always eat in the kitchen anyway.
谁会在饭厅吃饭啊
No one eats in the dining room.
我们时间不多了
We don't have a lot of time.
赶紧上飞船
So get your ass on a boat.
嘿 大家伙
Hey, big guy...
太阳就要落山了
The sun is getting real low.
你现在安全了 你会没事的  系好安全带
You're safe now. You're gonna be okay. Buckle up.
保护好你的装备 找个座位
Secure your gear, find a seat.
科斯嘉
Kostya?
我们刚刚还在超市里
We were in the market
科斯嘉
Kostya!
托尔 我要你回教堂一趟
Thor, I'm gonna need you back in the church.
- 这是最后一批了吗 - 是啊
- Is this the last of them? - Yeah.
- 所有人都上了飞船 - 如果这奏效的话
- Everyone else is on the carrier. - You know, if this works...
我们也许可以全身而退
we maybe don't walk away.
也许不呢
Maybe not.
我已挣脱提线 便要及时行乐
I have no strings, so I have fun...
再也不受谁人牵绊
I'm not tied up to anyone.
来吧 该走了
Come on. Time to go.
没料到我有这招吧
You didn't see that coming.
看在上帝的份上
Oh for God's sake!
- 兹琳卡 - 哦 科斯特尔 我的宝贝
-Zrinka! -Costel! Baby!
我没事
No, no. I'm fine.
好吧
Fine.
真是漫长的一天
It's been a long day.
旺达
Wanda.
如果你再不走 你会死在这里的
If you stay here, you'll die.
我已经死过一回了
I just did.
你知道那种感受怎么样吗
Do you know how it felt?
就像这样
It felt like that.
托尔 听我指示
Thor... on my mark.
就是现在
Now!
大家伙 我们成功了
Hey, big guy. We did it.
任务完成了
The job's finished.
我需要你驾驶这架飞机回来 好吗
Now I need you to turn this bird around, ok?
飞机处于隐身模式 我们追踪不了
We can't track you in stealth mode.
所以帮我个忙 我要你...
So help me out, I need you t...
你害怕了
You're afraid.
害怕你吗
Of you?
害怕死
Of death.
你是最后一个了
You're the last one.
本来应该是你
You're supposed to be the last.
史塔克想要创造个救世主
Stark asked for a savior...
却造出了个奴隶
and settled for a slave.
我猜我们都让人失望了
I suppose we're both disappointments.
我想也是
I suppose we are.
人类太奇怪了
Humans are odd.
他们觉得秩序和混乱是截然对立的
They think order and chaos are somehow opposites and...
还试图去操纵掌控之外的事情
try to control what won't be.
可他们的失败也不失优雅
But there's grace in their failings.
我觉得你忽略了这一点
I think you've missed that.
人类注定要灭绝
They're doomed.
也是
Yes...
但事物的美好并不在其永恒
but a thing isn't beautiful because it lasts.
我很荣幸是他们的一员
It's a privilege to be among them.
你真的太天真了
You're unbearably naive.
毕竟
Well,
我昨天才诞生
I was born yesterday.
和小娜阿姨打声招呼
Say hi to your Auntie Nat.
小胖子
Fat.
我们有个技术员标记了这个
One of our tech boys flagged this.
落在班达海
Splashed down in the Banda Sea.
有可能是奎因战机
Could be the Quin jet...
但是因为用了史塔克的隐身技术
but with Stark's stealth tech
我们还是追踪不到这东西
we still can't track the damn thing.
好吧
Right.
或许是跳下飞机游去了斐济岛
Probably jumped out and swam to Fiji.
他会寄明信片来的
He'll send a postcard.
你当时要是在就好了
Wish you were here.
之前是你指派我去招募他
You sent me to recruit him... way back when.
你那时知道现在会发生这种事吗
Did you know then what was gonna happen?
谁料得到
You never know...
你追求完美 你让我得到了
You hope for the best, and make do with what you get.
我手下这最棒的团队
I got a great team.
没有什么事物能天长地久
Nothing lasts forever.
麻烦可以 罗曼诺夫小姐
Trouble, Miss Romanoff...
不论谁胜谁负 麻烦总是接踵而来
No matter who wins or loses... trouble still comes 'round.
规则已经变了
The rules have changed...
我们正和新事物在打交道
we're dealing with something new.
幻视其实是人工智能
Well the Vision is artificial intelligence.
- 是一台机器 - 所以拿起锤子也不算是吗
- A machine. - So it doesn't count?
不算 拿起锤子的又不是人
No, it's not like a person lifting the hammer.
好吧 评判我们的规则是不同的
Right. Different rules for us.
- 人不错 但是个人工智能 - 谢谢捧场
- Nice guy... artificial. - Thank you
既然他能挥动锤子 他就能保管心灵宝石
He can wield the hammer. He can keep the mind stone.
它在幻视手里是安全的
It's safe with the Vision.
如今 安全也是一种奢侈了
These days safe is in short supply.
但如果把锤子放在电梯里
But if you put the hammer in an elevator.
- 还是会跟着电梯向上升 - 电梯可没资格拿起锤子
- It would still go up. - Elevator's not worthy
我会想念和你们拌嘴的日子的
I'm gonna miss these little talks of ours.
那就别走吧
Not if you don't leave.
我也没办法
I have no choice.
心灵宝石是近年来出现的
The mind stone is the fourth of the infinity stones
第四块无限宝石
to show up in the last few years.
这肯定不是巧合
It's not a coincidence.
肯定有人在背后操纵
Someone has been playing intricate games...
还利用了我们
and has made pawns of us.
一旦所有的宝石都集齐了
Once all these pieces are in position...
然后就同花顺吗
Triple Yahtzee?
你觉得能搞清楚会发生什么吗
You think you can find out what's coming?
是的
I do.
除了这家伙
Besides this one,
没什么解释不了的
there's nothing that can't be explained.
这家伙真是不把草坪养护当回事
That man has no regard for lawn maintenance.
但我还是会想他的 你也会想念我的
I'm gonna miss him though, and you're gonna miss me.
想必会流不少男儿泪吧
There's gonna be a lot of manful tears.
我会想你的 托尼
I will miss you, Tony.
是吗
Yeah?
我也该休息一下了
Well... It's time for me to tap out.
或许我向巴顿学习一下
Maybe I should take a page out of Barton's book.
给小辣椒建个农场 但愿没人想炸翻它
Build Pepper a farm... hope nobody blows it up.
简朴的生活
The simple life.
- 总有一天 你也会如愿的 - 我也不知道
- You'll get there one day. - I do not know.
家庭 安定下来
Family... stability...
那个梦想着这一切的男人 在七十五年前已被冰封了
Guy who wanted all that, went into the ice 75 years ago.
破冰而出的却是另一个人了
I think someone else came out.
你还好吧
You alright?
我感觉回到家了
I'm home.
你是想一直盯着这面墙 还是想去干活了
Wanna keep staring at the wall, or do you want to go to work?
说实话 这墙也挺吸引人的
I mean it's a pretty interesting wall.
我还想着你和托尼要缠绵多久呢
Thought you and Tony were still gazing into each others eyes.
我们情况如何
How do we look?
我们还不是最佳阵容
Well we're not the '27 Yankees.
但还是有些好手
We got some batters.
他们很优秀 但还不是个团队
They're good, but not a team.
好好磨练他们成形
Let's beat'em into shape.
复仇者们
Avengers....!
好吧
Fine.
我亲自出马
I'll do it myself.